<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../XML-XSL-DTD/Drama.xsl"?>
<!DOCTYPE note SYSTEM "books.dtd">

<library>
	<book>
		<Title> Malibu Rising </Title>
		<Summary> Four famous siblings throw an epic party to celebrate the end of the summer. But over the course of twenty-four hours, their lives will change forever.

Malibu: August, 1983. It’s the day of Nina Riva’s annual end-of-summer party, and anticipation is at a fever pitch. Everyone wants to be around the famous Rivas: Nina, the talented surfer and supermodel; brothers Jay and Hud, one a championship surfer, the other a renowned photographer; and their adored baby sister, Kit. Together, the siblings are a source of fascination in Malibu and the world over—especially as the offspring of the legendary singer, Mick Riva.

The only person not looking forward to the party of the year is Nina herself, who never wanted to be the center of attention, and who has also just been very publicly abandoned by her pro tennis player husband. Oh, and maybe Hud—because it is long past time to confess something to the brother from whom he’s been inseparable since birth.</Summary>
		<Pages> 369 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567896999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Taylor Jenkins Reid </Author>
		<Price> AED 28.10 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> The Last Letter </Title>
		<Summary> Beckett,

If you’re reading this, well, you know the last-letter drill. You made it. I didn’t. Get off the guilt train, because I know if there was any chance you could have saved me, you would have.

I need one thing from you: get out of the army and get to Telluride.

My little sister Ella’s raising the twins alone. She’s too independent and won’t accept help easily, but she has lost our grandmother, our parents, and now me. It’s too much for anyone to endure. It’s not fair.

And here’s the kicker: there’s something else you don’t know that’s tearing her family apart. She’s going to need help.

So if I’m gone, that means I can’t be there for Ella. I can’t help them through this. But you can. So I’m begging you, as my best friend, go take care of my sister, my family.

Please don’t make her go through it alone.

Ryan </Summary>
		<Pages> 426 </Pages>
		<ISBN> ‎123567894999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Rebecca Yarros </Author>
		<Price> AED 53.43 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> American Dirt </Title>
		<Summary> Jeanine Cummins's American Dirt, the #1 New York Times bestseller and Oprah Book Club pick that has sold over two million copies, is finally available in paperback.

Lydia lives in Acapulco. She has a son, Luca, the love of her life, and a wonderful husband who is a journalist. And while cracks are beginning to show in Acapulco because of the cartels, Lydia’s life is, by and large, fairly comfortable. But after her husband’s tell-all profile of the newest drug lord is published, none of their lives will ever be the same.

Forced to flee, Lydia and Luca find themselves joining the countless people trying to reach the United States. Lydia soon sees that everyone is running from something. But what exactly are they running to? </Summary>
		<Pages> 459 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567890999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Jeanine Cummins </Author>
		<Price> AED 41.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Magnolia Parks </Title>
		<Summary> She is a beautiful, affluent, self-involved and mildly neurotic London socialite. He is Britain's most photographed bad-boy lothario who broke her heart. But Magnolia Parks and BJ Ballentine are meant to be, and everyone knows it. They're in the stars... just suspended in a strange kind of love that looks like hurting each other a lot of the time: She dates other people to keep him at bay; he sleeps with other girls to get back at her for it. But at the end of their every sad endeavour to get over one another, it's still each other they crawl back to. But their dysfunction is catching up with them, pulling at their seams and fraying the world they've built; a world where neither has to ever let the other go completely. As the cracks start to show and secrets begin to surface, Magnolia and BJ are finally forced to face the formidable question they've been avoiding all their lives: how many loves do you really get in a lifetime? </Summary>
		<Pages> 423 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567895999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Jessa Hastings </Author>
		<Price> AED 33.77 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Heart Bones </Title>
		<Summary> Life and a dismal last name are the only two things Beyah Grim's parents ever gave her. After carving her path all on her own, Beyah is well on her way to bigger and better things, thanks to no one but herself.

With only two short months separating her from the future she's built and the past she desperately wants to leave behind, an unexpected death leaves Beyah with no place to go during the interim. Forced to reach out to her last resort, Beyah has to spend the remainder of her summer on a peninsula in Texas with a father she barely knows. Beyah's plan is to keep her head down and let the summer slip by seamlessly, but her new neighbor Samson throws a wrench in that plan.

Samson and Beyah have nothing in common on the surface. </Summary>
		<Pages> 338 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567892999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Colleen Hoover </Author>
		<Price> AED 28.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Hello Beautiful </Title>
		<Summary> An emotionally layered and engrossing story of a family that asks: Can love make a broken person whole?

William Waters grew up in a house silenced by tragedy, where his parents could hardly bear to look at him, much less love him. So it’s a relief when his skill on the basketball court earns him a scholarship to college, far away from his childhood home. He soon meets Julia Padavano, a spirited and ambitious young woman who surprises William with her appreciation of his quiet steadiness. With Julia comes her family; she is inseparable from her three younger sisters: Sylvie, the dreamer, is happiest with her nose in a book and imagines a future different from the expected path of wife and mother; Cecelia, the family’s artist; and Emeline, who patiently takes care of all of them. Happily, the Padavanos fold Julia’s new boyfriend into their loving, chaotic household. </Summary>
		<Pages> 416 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567893999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Ann Napolitano </Author>
		<Price> AED 51.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Until August </Title>
		<Summary> The extraordinary rediscovered novel from the Nobel Prize–winning author of Love in the Time of Cholera and One Hundred Years of Solitude
 
Sitting alone beside the languorous blue waters of the lagoon, Ana Magdalena Bach contemplates the men at the hotel bar. She has been happily married for twenty-seven years and has no reason to escape the life she has made with her husband and children. And yet, every August, she travels by ferry here to the island where her mother is buried, and for one night takes a new lover.
     Across sultry Caribbean evenings full of salsa and boleros, lotharios and conmen, Ana journeys further each year into the hinterland of her desire and the fear hidden in her heart.
     Constantly surprising, joyously sensual, Until August is a profound meditation on freedom, regret, self-transformation, and the mysteries of love—an unexpected gift from one of the greatest writers the world has ever known. </Summary>
		<Pages> 144 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567818999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Gabriel Garcia </Author>
		<Price> AED 53.43 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Apples Never Fall </Title>
		<Summary> From #1 New York Times bestselling author Liane Moriarty comes a novel that looks at marriage, siblings, and how the people we love the most can hurt us the deepest

The Delaney family love one another dearly—it’s just that sometimes they want to murder each other . . .

If your mother was missing, would you tell the police? Even if the most obvious suspect was your father?

This is the dilemma facing the four grown Delaney siblings.

The Delaneys are fixtures in their community. The parents, Stan and Joy, are the envy of all of their friends. They’re killers on the tennis court, and off it their chemistry is palpable. But after fifty years of marriage, they’ve finally sold their famed tennis academy and are ready to start what should be the golden years of their lives. So why are Stan and Joy so miserable? </Summary>
		<Pages> 467 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567891999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Liane Moriarty </Author>
		<Price> AED 29.50 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> The Stillwater Girls </Title>
		<Summary> Two sisters raised in fear are about to find out why in a chilling novel of psychological suspense from the author of The Thinnest Air.

Ignorant of civilization and cautioned against its evils, nineteen-year-old Wren and her two sisters, Sage and Evie, were raised in off-the-grid isolation in a primitive cabin in upstate New York. When the youngest grows gravely ill, their mother leaves with the child to get help from a nearby town. And they never return.

As months pass, hope vanishes. Supplies are low. Livestock are dying. A brutal winter is bearing down. Then comes the stranger. He claims to be looking for the girls’ mother, and he’s not leaving without them. </Summary>
		<Pages> 256 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567808999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Minka Kent </Author>
		<Price> AED 23.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> After Annie </Title>
		<Summary> When Annie Brown dies suddenly, her husband, her four young children and her closest friend are left to struggle without the woman who centered their lives. Bill Brown finds himself overwhelmed, and Annie’s best friend Annemarie is lost to old bad habits without Annie’s support. It is Annie’s daughter, Ali, forced to try to care for her younger brothers and even her father, who manages to maintain some semblance of their former lives for them all, and who confronts the complicated truths of adulthood.

Yet over the course of the next year, while Annie looms large in their memories, all three are able to grow, to change, even to become stronger and more sure of themselves. The enduring power Annie gave to those who loved her is the power to love, and to go on without her. </Summary>
		<Pages> 304 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567890899 </ISBN>
		<Author> Anna Quindlen </Author>
		<Price> AED 45.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> The Push </Title>
		<Summary> A tense, page-turning psychological drama about the making and breaking of a family–and a woman whose experience of motherhood is nothing at all what she hoped for–and everything she feared.

Blythe Connor is determined that she will be the warm, comforting mother to her new baby Violet that she herself never had.

But in the thick of motherhood’s exhausting early days, Blythe becomes convinced that something is wrong with her daughter–she doesn’t behave like most children do.

Or is it all in Blythe’s head? Her husband, Fox, says she’s imagining things. The more Fox dismisses her fears, the more Blythe begins to question her own sanity, and the more we begin to question what Blythe is telling us about her life as well. </Summary>
		<Pages> 307 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567898999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Ashley Audrain </Author>
		<Price> AED 24.15 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> The Paper Palace </Title>
		<Summary> It is a perfect July morning, and Elle, a fifty-year-old happily married mother of three, awakens at "The Paper Palace"—the family summer place which she has visited every summer of her life. But this morning is different: last night Elle and her oldest friend Jonas crept out the back door into the darkness and had sex with each other for the first time, all while their spouses chatted away inside.

Now, over the next twenty-four hours, Elle will have to decide between the life she has made with her genuinely beloved husband, Peter, and the life she always imagined she would have had with her childhood love, Jonas, if a tragic event hadn't forever changed the course of their lives. </Summary>
		<Pages> 400 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567897999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Miranda Cowley Heller </Author>
		<Price> AED 25.00 </Price>
	</book>
</library>
