<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../XML-XSL-DTD/Fiction.xsl"?>
<!DOCTYPE note SYSTEM "books.dtd">

<library>
	<book>
		<Title> 1984 </Title>
		<Summary> A masterpiece of rebellion and imprisonment where war is peace freedom is slavery and Big Brother is watching Thought Police Big Brother Orwellian. These words have entered our vocabulary because of George Orwell's classic dystopian novel 1984. The story of one man's nightmare odyssey as he pursues a forbidden love affair through a world ruled by warring states and a power structure that controls not only information but also individual thought and memory. 1984 is a prophetic haunting tale. More relevant than ever before 1984 exposes the worst crimes imaginable the destruction of truth freedom and individuality With a foreword by Thomas Pynchon. With a foreword by Thomas Pynchon. A masterpiece of rebellion and imprisonment where war is peace freedom is slavery and Big Brother is watching View our feature on George Orwell's 1984. This beautiful paperback edition features deckled edges and french flaps a perfect gift for any occasion. </Summary>
		<Pages> 368 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567298999 </ISBN>
		<Author> George Orwell	 </Author>
		<Price> AED 80.91 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> The Alchemist </Title>
		<Summary> Combining magic, mysticism, wisdom, and wonder into an inspiring tale of self-discovery, The Alchemist has become a modern classic, selling millions of copies around the world and transforming the lives of countless readers across generations.

Paulo Coelho's masterpiece tells the mystical story of Santiago, an Andalusian shepherd boy who yearns to travel in search of a worldly treasure. His quest will lead him to riches far different—and far more satisfying—than he ever imagined. Santiago's journey teaches us about the essential wisdom of listening to our hearts, recognizing opportunity and learning to read the omens strewn along life's path, and, most importantly, following our dreams. </Summary>
		<Pages> 182 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567198999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Paulo Coelho </Author>
		<Price> AED 84.47 </Price>
	</book>

	<book>
		<Title> The Help </Title>
		<Summary> Three ordinary women are about to take one extraordinary step.

Twenty-two-year-old Skeeter has just returned home after graduating from Ole Miss. She may have a degree, but it is 1962, Mississippi, and her mother will not be happy till Skeeter has a ring on her finger. Skeeter would normally find solace with her beloved maid Constantine, the woman who raised her, but Constantine has disappeared and no one will tell Skeeter where she has gone.

Aibileen is a black maid, a wise, regal woman raising her seventeenth white child. Something has shifted inside her after the loss of her own son, who died while his bosses looked the other way. She is devoted to the little girl she looks after, though she knows both their hearts may be broken.

Minny, Aibileen's best friend, is short, fat, and perhaps the sassiest woman in Mississippi. She can cook like nobody's business, but she can't mind her tongue, so she's lost yet another job. Minny finally finds a position working for someone too new to town to know her reputation. But her new boss has secrets of her own. </Summary>
		<Pages> 464 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 	123567878999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Kathryn Stockett </Author>
		<Price> AED 71.24 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Jane Eyre </Title>
		<Summary> A gothic masterpiece of tempestuous passions and dark secrets, Charlotte Brontë's Jane Eyre is edited with an introduction and notes by Stevie Davis in Penguin Classics.

Charlotte Brontë tells the story of orphaned Jane Eyre, who grows up in the home of her heartless aunt, enduring loneliness and cruelty. This troubled childhood strengthens Jane's natural independence and spirit - which prove necessary when she finds employment as a governess to the young ward of Byronic, brooding Mr Rochester. As her feelings for Rochester develop, Jane gradually uncovers Thornfield Hall's terrible secret, forcing her to make a choice. Should she stay with Rochester and live with the consequences, or follow her convictions - even if it means leaving the man she loves? A novel of intense power and intrigue, Jane Eyre dazzled readers with its passionate depiction of a woman's search for equality and freedom. </Summary>
		<Pages> 532 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 	123567868999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Charlotte Bronte </Author>
		<Price> AED 40.40 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> The Kite Runner </Title>
		<Summary> 1970s Afghanistan: Twelve-year-old Amir is desperate to win the local kite-fighting tournament and his loyal friend Hassan promises to help him. But neither of the boys can foresee what would happen to Hassan that afternoon, an event that is to shatter their lives. After the Russians invade and the family is forced to flee to America, Amir realises that one day he must return to an Afghanistan under Taliban rule to find the one thing that his new world cannot grant him: redemption. </Summary>
		<Pages> 371 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 	123567858999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Khaled Hosseini </Author>
		<Price> AED 34.04 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Dune </Title>
		<Summary> Set on the desert planet Arrakis, Dune is the story of the boy Paul Atreides, heir to a noble family tasked with ruling an inhospitable world where the only thing of value is the “spice” melange, a drug capable of extending life and enhancing consciousness. Coveted across the known universe, melange is a prize worth killing for...

When House Atreides is betrayed, the destruction of Paul’s family will set the boy on a journey toward a destiny greater than he could ever have imagined. And as he evolves into the mysterious man known as Muad’Dib, he will bring to fruition humankind’s most ancient and unattainable dream. </Summary>
		<Pages> 658 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 	123567998999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Frank Herbert </Author>
		<Price> AED 48.56 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Mockingjay </Title>
		<Summary> Katniss Everdeen, girl on fire, has survived, even though her home has been destroyed. Gale has escaped. Katniss's family is safe. Peeta has been captured by the Capitol. Distric 13 really does exist. There are rebels. There are new leaders. A revolution is unfolding.

It is by design that Katniss was rescued from the arena in the cruel and haunting Quarter Quell, and it is by design that she has long been part of the revolution without knowing it. District 13 has come out of the shadows and is plotting to overthrow the Captiol. Everyone, it seems, has had a hand in the carefully laid plans - except Katniss.

The success of the rebellion hinges on Katniss's willingness to be a pawn, to accept responsibility for countless lives, and to change the course of the future of Panem. To do this,s he must put aside her feelings of anger and distrust. She must become the rebels' Mockingjay - no matter what the personal cost. </Summary>
		<Pages> 400 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 	123567838999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Suzanne Collins </Author>
		<Price> AED 24.15 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> The Giver </Title>
		<Summary> The Giver is a 1993 American young adult dystopian novel written by Lois Lowry, set in a society which at first appears to be utopian but is revealed to be dystopian as the story progresses. At the age of twelve, Jonas, a young boy from a seemingly utopian, futuristic world, is singled out to receive special training from The Giver, who alone holds the memories of the true joys and pain of life.In the novel, the society has taken away pain and strife by converting to "Sameness", a plan that has also eradicated emotional depth from their lives. In an effort to preserve order, the society also lacks any color, climate, terrain, and a true sense of equality. The protagonist of the story, a 12-year-old boy named Jonas, is selected to inherit the position of Receiver of Memory, the person who stores all the memories of the time before Sameness. Jonas struggles with concepts of the new emotions and things introduced to him, and whether they are inherently good, evil, or in between, and whether it is possible to have one without the other. </Summary>
		<Pages> 208 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 	123567898999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Lois Lowry </Author>
		<Price> AED 29.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Animal Farm </Title>
		<Summary> A farm is taken over by its overworked, mistreated animals. With flaming idealism and stirring slogans, they set out to create a paradise of progress, justice, and equality. Thus the stage is set for one of the most telling satiric fables ever penned –a razor-edged fairy tale for grown-ups that records the evolution from revolution against tyranny to a totalitarianism just as terrible.
When Animal Farm was first published, Stalinist Russia was seen as its target. Today it is devastatingly clear that wherever and whenever freedom is attacked, under whatever banner, the cutting clarity and savage comedy of George Orwell’s masterpiece have a meaning and message still ferociously fresh. </Summary>
		<Pages> 141 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 	123567098999 </ISBN>
		<Author> George Orwell </Author>
		<Price> AED 10.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> The Martian </Title>
		<Summary> Six days ago, astronaut Mark Watney became one of the first people to walk on Mars.

Now, he’s sure he’ll be the first person to die there.

After a dust storm nearly kills him and forces his crew to evacuate while thinking him dead, Mark finds himself stranded and completely alone with no way to even signal Earth that he’s alive—and even if he could get word out, his supplies would be gone long before a rescue could arrive.

Chances are, though, he won’t have time to starve to death. The damaged machinery, unforgiving environment, or plain-old “human error” are much more likely to kill him first.

But Mark isn’t ready to give up yet. Drawing on his ingenuity, his engineering skills — and a relentless, dogged refusal to quit — he steadfastly confronts one seemingly insurmountable obstacle after the next. Will his resourcefulness be enough to overcome the impossible odds against him? </Summary>
		<Pages> 384 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 	123567848999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Andy Weir </Author>
		<Price> AED 39.16 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Station Eleven </Title>
		<Summary> An audacious, darkly glittering novel set in the eerie days of civilization’s collapse—the spellbinding story of a Hollywood star, his would-be savior, and a nomadic group of actors roaming the scattered outposts of the Great Lakes region, risking everything for art and humanity.

Kirsten Raymonde will never forget the night Arthur Leander, the famous Hollywood actor, had a heart attack on stage during a production of King Lear. That was the night when a devastating flu pandemic arrived in the city, and within weeks, civilization as we know it came to an end.

Twenty years later, Kirsten moves between the settlements of the altered world with a small troupe of actors and musicians. They call themselves The Traveling Symphony, and they have dedicated themselves to keeping the remnants of art and humanity alive. But when they arrive in St. Deborah by the Water, they encounter a violent prophet who will threaten the tiny band’s existence. And as the story takes off, moving back and forth in time, and vividly depicting life before and after the pandemic, the strange twist of fate that connects them all will be revealed. </Summary>
		<Pages> 333 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 	123567828999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Emily St. John Mandel </Author>
		<Price> AED 65.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Gone Girl </Title>
		<Summary> Who are you?
What have we done to each other?

These are the questions Nick Dunne finds himself asking on the morning of his fifth wedding anniversary when his wife Amy suddenly disappears. The police suspect Nick. Amy's friends reveal that she was afraid of him, that she kept secrets from him. He swears it isn't true. A police examination of his computer shows strange searches. He says they weren't made by him. And then there are the persistent calls on his mobile phone.

So what did happen to Nick's beautiful wife? </Summary>
		<Pages> 415 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 	123567888999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Gillian Flynn </Author>
		<Price> AED 44.05 </Price>
	</book>
</library>
