<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../XML-XSL-DTD/Humour.xsl"?>
<!DOCTYPE note SYSTEM "books.dtd">

<library>
	<book>
		<Title> Heart to Heart </Title>
		<Summary> Applying to be a contestant on a reality dating show is the last thing I ever thought I would do…Well, aside from actually being on a reality dating show, that is. But here I am on Heart to Heart, hoping to come in second place.

Yes, second place.

I know how crazy that sounds, especially since this season’s love interest is none other than Tristan Tate, my teenage crush.  I just have to get through this reality television gig, win viewers over, and not fall for any of the contestants. If I can manage that, I’ll have my career back, provided a wrench doesn’t get thrown into the whole thing.

Enter Avery Martin: the wrench. Avery stumbled into my life, quite literally, and I haven’t been able to get her out of my mind since then.

And that’s a huge problem. </Summary>
		<Pages> 370 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123569798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Sara Furlong Burr </Author>
		<Price> AED 64.95 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Bunt! </Title>
		<Summary> Molly Bauer's first year of college is not the picture-perfect piece of art she'd always envisioned. On day one at PICA, Molly discovers that—through some horrible twist of fate—her full-ride scholarship has vanished! But the ancient texts (PICA's dusty financial aid documents) reveal a loophole. If Molly and 9 other art students win a single game of softball, they'll receive a massive athletic scholarship. Can Molly's crew of ragtag artists succeed in softball without dropping the ball?

The author of the New York Times best-selling Check, Please series, Ngozi Ukazu returns with debut artist Madeline Rupert to bring an energetic young adult story about authenticity, old vs. new, and college failure. It also poses the question: “Is art school worth it?” </Summary>
		<Pages> 288 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123563798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Ngozi Ukazu </Author>
		<Price> AED 45.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Buffalo Fluffalo </Title>
		<Summary> Introducing a sweet and silly buffalo who tries to bluff and fluff his way into being bigger than he really is. This laugh-out-loud story by an Emmy-nominated comedy writer shows it’s okay to be yourself.

I’m the Buffalo Fluffalo
I heave and I huffalo
Leave me alone because
I’ve had enuffalo.

Buffalo Fluffalo arrives on the scene puffed up with self-importance. Stomping around and raising billows of dust, Buffalo Fluffalo proclaims his superiority to the other creatures—the ram, the prairie dog, and the crow—who just want to be his friend. So Buffalo Fluffalo, who has had enuffalo , heads off to grumble to himself. </Summary>
		<Pages> 10 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123564798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Bess Kalb </Author>
		<Price> AED 110.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Really Good, Actually </Title>
		<Summary> A hilarious and painfully relatable debut novel about one woman’s messy search for joy and meaning in the wake of an unexpected breakup, from comedian, essayist, and award-winning screenwriter Monica Heisey

Maggie is fine. She’s doing really good, actually. Sure, she’s broke, her graduate thesis on something obscure is going nowhere, and her marriage only lasted 608 days, but at the ripe old age of twenty-nine, Maggie is determined to embrace her new life as a Surprisingly Young Divorcée™.

Now she has time to take up nine hobbies, eat hamburgers at 4 am, and “get back out there” sex-wise. With the support of her tough-loving academic advisor, Merris; her newly divorced friend, Amy; and her group chat (naturally), Maggie barrels through her first year of single life, intermittently dating, occasionally waking up on the floor and asking herself tough questions along the way. </Summary>
		<Pages> 370 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567698999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Monica Heisey </Author>
		<Price> AED 45.90 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Subculture Vulture </Title>
		<Summary> A riotous, whirlwind tour through deep American subcultures ranging from Burning Man to Alcoholics Anonymous, by the writer and comedian Moshe Kasher

After bottoming out, being institutionalized, and getting sober all by the tender age of fifteen, Moshe Kasher found himself “What’s next?” Over the ensuing decades, he discovered the a lot.

There was his time as a boy-king of Alcoholics Anonymous, a kind of pubescent proselytizer for other teens getting and staying sober. He was a rave promoter turned DJ turned sober ecstasy dealer in San Francisco’s techno warehouse party scene of the 1990s. For fifteen years he worked as a psychedelic security guard at Burning Man, fishing hippies out of hidden chambers they’d constructed to try to sneak into the event. As a child of deaf parents, Kasher became deeply immersed in deaf culture and sign language interpretation, translating everything from end-of-life care to horny deaf clients’ attempts to hire sex workers. He reconnects and tries to make peace with his ultra-Hasidic Jewish upbringing after the death of his father before finally settling into the comedy scene where he now makes his living. </Summary>
		<Pages> 320 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567598999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Moshe Kasher </Author>
		<Price> AED 28.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Swanna in Love </Title>
		<Summary> Best-selling author Belle ( High Maintenance, Going Down) unleashes her first new novel in over ten years
It's the summer of 1982 and fourteen-year-old Swanna Swain is the only one left at camp. The place is a ghost town by the time her mother Val finally shows up six hours late—stoned and radiant—in a Ford pickup driven by Borislav, her new young Russian lover. Assuming she is headed home to her air-conditioned Upper West Side apartment, Swanna and her lovable younger brother Madding are instead dragged to Vermont—to an artist colony where kids are not welcome and they are forced to sleep in the back of the truck, while Val is cozy inside the house with the Russian.
Then Swanna meets Dennis, a handsome married father of two, at a bowling alley, and, knowing a thing or two about seduction from Judy Blume, her best friend at camp, and her own parents’ many affairs—she sets out to convince Dennis to help her. But love seldom obeys rules, and even a tough, smart, city girl like Swanna might not be able to handle falling in love.
Best-selling novelist Jennifer Belle returns with a kind of inverse Lolita that explores adolescent desire from the girl’s point of view. In turns hilarious and wildly shocking, Swanna In Love will keep your feathers ruffled and the pages gliding by. </Summary>
		<Pages> 288 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567498999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Jennifer Belle </Author>
		<Price> AED 33.64 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> The Lede </Title>
		<Summary> A fascinating, opinionated portrait of journalism and the people who make it, told through pieces collected from the incomparable six-decade career of bestselling author and beloved New Yorker writer Calvin Trillin

“A literary treasure.”— The Washington Times

I’ve been writing about the press almost as long as I’ve been in the game. At some point, it occurred to me that disparate pieces from various places in various styles amounted to a picture from multiple angles of what the press has been like over the years since I became a practitioner and an observer.

Calvin Trillin has reported serious pieces across America for The New Yorker , covered the civil rights movement in the South for Time , and written comic verse for The Nation . But one of his favorite subjects over the years—a superb fit for his unique combination of reportage and humor—has been his own professional the American press. </Summary>
		<Pages> 336 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123568798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Calvin Trillin </Author>
		<Price> AED 151.47 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Haunted Holiday </Title>
		<Summary> Giant battle robots! Cotton candy betrayal! Blasts from the past! And the ultimate challenge to stay true to themselves and each other await Theo and Alexander in the final book in the tragic series about the Sinister-Winterbottom twins, who must solve one wretched mystery after the next.

Trapped in Aunt Saffronia’s spectral house, Theo and Alexander must work together to escape, stop their newfound nemesis Essa and her henchman Edgaren’t, save Wil and their friends, find their parents, and maybe, just maybe, get things back to normal.

Following the clues left behind, the twins find themselves at Siren’s Song Seaside Amusement Park. Old faces and new surprises await them in a park that was built to lure in visitors… and their secrets. </Summary>
		<Pages> 267 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123560798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Kiersten White </Author>
		<Price> AED 97.88 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> My Dark Desire </Title>
		<Summary> The task was simple.
Sneak into Potomac’s most heavily guarded manor.
Steal back my pendant. Slip out.

Problem number one?
America’s most unattainable bachelor caught me.

Problem number two?
He decided to keep me. As the help.

Zachary Sun’s winter may be the coldest I’ve ever felt,
but he makes my skin burn.

Reserved, calculated, and savagely cruel,
he thrives on the weaknesses of others.

Little does he know, he just met his match.

He may be American royalty.
But this peasant will rise to become Queen.

Authors’ Notes: My Dark Desire is a standalone double-grump romance between a broken billionaire and a feisty maid unafraid to fight back. It is set in the decadent Dark Prince Road world. </Summary>
		<Pages> 426 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> L.J Shen </Author>
		<Price> AED 32.09 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Blank </Title>
		<Summary> A wife, mother, and frustrated writer faces an impossible deadline for turning her life around in a hilarious debut novel about family, friendship, success, and exhilarating self-(re)discovery. Pippa Jones is a fortyish former literary sensation who fears she will be a one-hit wonder. After the follow-up book she was almost done writing, Podlusters , had to be tossed (it ended up sharing a plot and title with superstar author Ella Rankin’s summer blockbuster!), she couldn’t write a thing. Months of staring at a blank page made her confidence vanish like a one-night stand. When she finds out that she has only five days left to finish (or rather, start ) or repay an advance she’s already spent, Pippa has a brilliantly original idea. Okay, fine, her twelve-year-old son came up with it as a joke, but Pippa and her teenage daughter approved. Pippa’s not only going to make a bold statement, but she’ll change the book world while she’s at it! Can she pull it off? </Summary>
		<Pages> 234 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567398999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Zibby Owens </Author>
		<Price> AED 20.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Dirty Thirty </Title>
		<Summary> Stephanie Plum, Trenton’s hardest working, most underappreciated bounty hunter, is offered a freelance assignment that seems simple enough. Local jeweler Martin Rabner wants her to locate his former security guard, Andy Manley (a.k.a. Nutsy), who he is convinced stole a fortune in diamonds out of his safe. Stephanie is also looking for another troubled man, Duncan Dugan, a fugitive from justice arrested for robbing the same jewelry store on the same day.

With her boyfriend Morelli away in Miami on police business, Stephanie is taking care of Bob, Morelli’s giant orange dog who will devour anything, from Stephanie’s stray donuts to the upholstery in her car. Morelli’s absence also means the inscrutable, irresistible security expert Ranger is front and center in Stephanie’s life when things inevitably go sideways. And he seems determined to stay there.

To complicate matters, her best friend Lula is convinced she is being stalked by a mythological demon hell-bent on relieving her of her wardrobe. </Summary>
		<Pages> 336 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123562798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Janet Evanovich </Author>
		<Price> AED 123.59 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Dog Man </Title>
		<Summary> Our canine superhero returns in DOG MAN: THE SCARLET SHEDDER, the suspenseful and hilarious twelfth graphic novel in the #1 worldwide bestselling series by award-winning author and illustrator Dav Pilkey!

P.U.! Dog Man got sprayed by a skunk! After being dunked in tomato juice, the stink is gone but the scarlet red color remains. Now exiled, this spunky superhero must struggle to save the citizens who shunned him! Will the ends justify the means for Petey, who's reluctantly pulled back into a life of crime in order to help Dog Man? And who will step forward when an all-new, never-before-seen villain unleashes an army of A.I. robots? </Summary>
		<Pages> 288 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123561798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Dav Pilkey </Author>
		<Price> AED 27.00 </Price>
	</book>
</library>
