<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../XML-XSL-DTD/Kids.xsl"?>
<!DOCTYPE note SYSTEM "books.dtd">

<library>
	<book>
		<Title> Waverider </Title>
		<Summary> The highly anticipated, thrilling conclusion to Kazu Kibuishi's #1 New York Times bestselling series! After her confrontation with Ikol, Emily finally understands the stone's power and what she must do to defend Alledia from the shadows. As she travels to Typhon to help her mom and Navin, Prince Trellis returns to the Kingdom of the Elves to save his countrymen -- and confront the fraud who has seized power in the absence of a king. The threat of darkness follows all Stonekeepers closely, and it will take the strength of both new friends and old foes to conquer it... and survive.Waverider is the final installment to the Amulet graphic novel series by Kazu Kibuishi. The story centered on Emily and Navin Hayes as they reach a conclusion in the futile war disrupting Alledia. It was released on February 6th, 2024. </Summary>
		<Pages> 256 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123566798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Kazu Kibuishi </Author>
		<Price> AED 57.33 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Medusa </Title>
		<Summary> From National Book Award finalist Katherine Percy Jackson meets The Troubled Girls of Dragomir Academy  in this fantastical adventure about Ava, who attends a boarding school for the descendants of Greek monsters and uncovers a terrible secret that could change the world forever. Ava Baldwin has always tried to keep her anger in check, just like her mom taught her. But when know-it-all classmate Owen King tries to speak over her yet again, Ava explodes . . . and Owen freezes, becoming totally unresponsive. Although Owen recovers, Ava's parents whisk her off to her mother’s alma mater, the Accademia del Forte, a mysterious international boarding school in Venice. There, Ava and her brother, Jax, discover that the Olympian gods founded the Accademia to teach the descendants of mythological monsters how to control their emotions and their powers and become functioning, well-adjusted members of society. But not everything at the Accademia is as it seems. After her friend Fia is almost expelled for challenging a teacher, Ava realizes the school is hiding a dangerous secret. To uncover the truth, Ava and her new friends embark on an adventure that could change the way they view history, mythology—and themselves—forever…or end their lives. </Summary>
		<Pages> 288 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123586798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Katherine Marsh </Author>
		<Price> AED 12.40 </Price>
	</book>

	<book>
		<Title> Finally Heard </Title>
		<Summary> From the New York Times bestselling author of Front Desk comes the sequel to Finally Seen in which Lina struggles to separate fact from fiction on social media.
						When ten-year-old Lina Gao sees her mom’s video on social media take off, she’s captivated by the potential to be seen and heard! Maybe online she can finally find the confidence she craves. Whereas in real life she’s growing so fast, she feels like microwave popcorn, bursting out of her skin!
						With the help of her two best friends, Carla and Finn, and her little sister, Millie, Lina sets off to go viral. Except there’s a lot more to social media than Lina ever imagined. </Summary>
		<Pages> 352 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123546798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Kelly Yang </Author>
		<Price> AED 9.45 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Averil Offline </Title>
		<Summary> A fun, fast-paced story about a girl determined to cut the cord with her helicopter parents.

Twelve-year-old coder Averil can't do anything without her parents knowing. That’s because her mom uses the Ruby Slippers surveillance app to check where she is, who she texts, and even what she eats for lunch. Averil wonders how she’s ever going to grow up if she’s not allowed to learn from mistakes. When she learns that Ruby Slippers is about to become even more invasive, she teams up with Max, a new kid at school dealing with overbearing parents of his own. Together they figure out an almost foolproof way to ditch their parents and run away to the college campus that’s home to the quirky Ruby Slippers creator. It’s an extreme challenge just getting to meet with him—but the two kids cleverly figure out a series of puzzles and get their meeting. What they find gives them pause—and gets them thinking about the value of honesty in a new light. After all, isn’t trust at the heart of their parents' need to know? </Summary>
		<Pages> 208 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123656798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Amy Noelle Parks </Author>
		<Price> AED 23.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Hummingbird Season </Title>
		<Summary> A poignant and necessary story about finding hope during difficult times, set in the early days of the Covid-19 pandemic.

Archie's life--and the whole world--is turned upside down by Covid-19. Suddenly there are no more Friday night dinners out, no more going to school, no more hanging out with friends . . . no leaving the house at all.

Even though he's inside with his family all day every day, Archie can't help but feel more alone than ever before. While everyone else seems to be adapting to their new normal just fine, it's like Archie is permanently on mute, unable to find the words to describe how he feels--and sometimes, unable to find someone who will listen. The bright spot of Archie's days at home is watching and learning about the hummingbirds that feed outside his windows. But just when it seems like this could be what brings his family together again, California experiences its worst wildfire in history, and Archie's favorite hummingbird disappears. In a time when hope is hard to hold on to, Archie must find his voice and find hope once again. </Summary>
		<Pages> 272 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123526798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Stephanie V.W Lucianovic </Author>
		<Price> AED 8.99 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Kitten Ninja </Title>
		<Summary> Fans of comics, and heartwarming stories—not to mention cats!—will love Kitten Ninja, the origin story of the incredible Cat Ninja!
						Before Cat Ninja grew up and became Metro City’s greatest defender, he was tiny, adorable Kitten Ninja and he battled...much tinier foes. (Hey, everybody has to start somewhere, right?)
						In this spin-off prequel to the enormously popular Epic Original Cat Ninja series, our favorite feline hero takes on everything a kitten-size ninja has to battle on the way to his heroic a sun spot that won’t stay put, an irresistible ball of yarn, and—every cat’s archenemy—snow! </Summary>
		<Pages> 80 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123596798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Collen A.F. Venable </Author>
		<Price> AED 4.56 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Sally's New Look </Title>
		<Summary> Sally is going to the groomer! Lovable pup Sally is looking a little shaggy, so her owners are taking her to the groomer. It smells like a garden and Sally sees brushes and bows galore. Then it's time for a bath. Once she's squeaky clean and blow-dried, Sally gets brushed, snipped and clipped. When her owners arrive―surprise!―everyone has fancy new hairdos! </Summary>
		<Pages> 32 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123576798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Andrew Larsen </Author>
		<Price> AED 20.23 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Wonka </Title>
		<Summary> WONKA tells the wondrous story of how the world's greatest inventor, magician and chocolate-maker becomes the beloved Willy Wonka we know today.
						Based on the upcoming Warner Bros. Pictures movie WONKA, created by Paul King and written for film by Simon Farnaby and Paul King.
						An intoxicating mix of magic and music, mayhem and emotion, all told with fabulous heart and humour - WONKA introduces readers to a young Willy Wonka, chock-full of ideas and determined to change the world one delectable bite at a time . . . proving that the best things in life begin with a dream, and if you're lucky enough to meet Willy Wonka, anything is possible. </Summary>
		<Pages> 328 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123565798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Roald Dahl </Author>
		<Price> AED 99.78 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> The Ickabog </Title>
		<Summary> Once upon a time there was a tiny kingdom called Cornucopia, as rich in happiness as it was in gold, and famous for its food. From the delicate cream cheeses of Kurdsburg to the Hopes-of-Heaven pastries of Chouxville, each was so delicious that people wept with joy as they ate them.
						But even in this happy kingdom, a monster lurks. Legend tells of a fearsome creature living far to the north in the Marshlands... the Ickabog. Some say it breathes fire, spits poison, and roars through the mist as it carries off wayward sheep and children alike. Some say it's just a myth... </Summary>
		<Pages> 290 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123516798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> J.K. Rowling </Author>
		<Price> AED 27.09 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Invisible </Title>
		<Summary> Emotional, moving, different... Invisible tells, through the eyes of a child, a story that could be that of any of us.
						Who hasn't ever wanted to be invisible?
						Who hasn't ever wanted to stop being one?
						The problem is that I have never managed to control that power well:
						Sometimes, when I most wanted to be invisible, that was when the most people saw me, and on the other hand, when I wanted everyone to see me, that was when my body wanted to disappear. </Summary>
		<Pages> 296 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123506798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Eloy Moreno </Author>
		<Price> AED 31.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Break </Title>
		<Summary> Olive is less-than-excited to be spending Spring Break stuck with her dad...will she be able to make the most of her trip, or will everything break apart?
						Spring Break is full of possibilities...but not for Olive.
						This year, Olive is leaving her friends and all of their exciting vacation plans behind to visit her dad at his new apartment in the city.
						Goober is thrilled to spend a whole week with their father and has a long list of activities for their time together. Olive, on the other hand, still remembers the hurt of their dad moving halfway across the world. She would rather spend time with her friend Bree or scrolling through her new phone to keep up with everything she's missing back home than catch up with him. </Summary>
		<Pages> 224 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123556798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Kayla Miller </Author>
		<Price> AED 29.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Hollowpox </Title>
		<Summary> Morrigan Crow and her friends have survived their first year as proud scholars of the elite Wundrous Society, helped bring down the nefarious Ghastly Market, and proven themselves loyal to Unit 919. Now Morrigan faces a new, exciting challenge: to master the mysterious Wretched Arts, and control the power that threatens to consume her.
						But a strange and frightening illness has taken hold of Nevermoor, turning infected Wunimals into mindless, vicious Unnimals on the hunt. As victims of the Hollowpox multiply, panic spreads. And with the city she loves in a state of fear, Morrigan quickly realizes it's up to her to find a cure for the Hollowpox, even if it will put her - and everyone in Nevermoor - in more danger than she ever imagined. </Summary>
		<Pages> 471 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123536798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Jessica Townsend </Author>
		<Price> AED 33.56 </Price>
	</book>
</library>
