<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../XML-XSL-DTD/Home.xsl"?>
<!DOCTYPE note SYSTEM "mainbooks.dtd">

<library>
	<book category="action">
		<Title> Kindling </Title>
		<Genre> Action </Genre>
		<Summary> From bestselling and award-winning author Traci Chee comes a standalone fantasy set against a war-ravaged world where kindling warfare—the use of elite, magic-wielding teenage soldiers—has been outlawed. In this rich and evocative novel, seven kindlings search for purpose and identity as they prepare for one final battle. For fans of the classic films Seven Samurai and The Magnificent Seven. Once, the war was fought with kindlings—elite, magic-wielding warriors whose devastating power comes at the cost of their own young lives. </Summary>
		<Pages> 423 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567890199 </ISBN>
		<Author> Traci Chee </Author>
		<Price> AED 102.78 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="action">
		<Title> Fatal Witness </Title>
		<Genre> Action </Genre>
		<Summary> As a child, artist and potter Dani Bennett witnessed the brutal murder of her parents. With no memory of the incident or her true identity, she was forced to take on a new name and a new life, hidden away in Montana for the past 25 years. Mae Richmond has spent the same stretch of time searching for her granddaughter, who went missing the night her daughter and son-in-law were murdered. Convinced the woman she saw in a pottery magazine feature is the woman she's been searching for, she enlists the help of K-9 officer Mark Lassiter of Pearl Springs, Tennessee, who tracks Dani down. </Summary>
		<Pages> 400 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567890189 </ISBN>
		<Author> Patricia Bradley </Author>
		<Price> AED 22.00 </Price>
	</book>

	<book category="action">
		<Title> Kingpin </Title>
		<Genre> Action </Genre>
		<Summary> The latest pulse-pounding thriller from Edgar and Barry Award finalist Mike Lawson starring his beloved Washington DC “troubleshooter” Joe DeMarco. Carson Newman doesn’t wear tracksuits. He doesn’t have a consigliere or operate out of the back room of a restaurant. And as evidenced by his ever-growing Boston empire, he doesn’t get his hands dirty. Usually. Joe DeMarco, on the other hand, is paid to get his hands dirty. So, when John Mahoney, the former Speaker of the House, calls, DeMarco knows it’s time to get to work. Brian Lewis, an intern for Mahoney, has been found dead, seemingly from a drug overdose. But Brian didn’t seem like a drug user, and even more concerning, he seemed to be on the cusp of releasing a report that identified a group of politicians who had taken bribes in helping dismantle a recent bill.  Brian’s mom is convinced that Brian was murdered because of what he’d learned, and it doesn’t take long for DeMarco to come to a similar conclusion. In a city full of shadowy agreements and duplicitous deals, DeMarco will soon learn that to get to the bottom of Brian’s death, he’ll have to look at people perched the very top of the world. </Summary>
		<Pages> 282 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 	123567890299 </ISBN>
		<Author> Mike Lawson </Author>
		<Price> AED 51.37 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="action">
		<Title> Blood Weaver </Title>
		<Genre> Action </Genre>
		<Summary> As the last female blood mage, many would kill to claim the power surging through her veins.
		For years Leila has hidden.
		she is.
		Where she came from.
		What she can do.
		But the long-lost Princess refuses to run forever. Those she loves lied to her. Betrayed her for a greater good. Even in her absence, she's being used as a pawn in political power plays.Now, Leila is determined to discover why.Thrust into a world she no longer remembers, Leila must fight to discover who she can trust as malicious threats close in from all sides. In a world where the past casts long shadows, Leila will discover that the threads of fate can be rewoven … but not without a cost. </Summary>
		<Pages> 268 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567890149 </ISBN>
		<Author> Karina Espinosa </Author>
		<Price> AED 20.10 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="action">
		<Title> Dark Dive </Title>
		<Genre> Action </Genre>
		<Summary> A Wall Street Journal bestselling series. Searching for a missing diver takes a Florida detective on a deep-diving adventure in a gripping thriller by the Amazon Charts bestselling author of Sea Castle . After the Underwater Investigation Unit’s disbandment, public outcry ushers Sloan McPherson and her partner, former navy diver Scott Hughes, back into the depths of crime solving. But Sloan’s return comes with a personal case. Longtime family friend Fred Stafford has disappeared. Left his abandoned truck in the vicinity of an unmarked sinkhole and new findings that have Sloan second-guessing everything she thought she knew about the man. There are his gambling debts, his association with a treasure-hunting band of underwater cavern junkies called the Dive Rats, and most alarming of all, a discovery in Stafford’s storage shed that raises the stakes even higher and plunges Sloan into an unfathomable mystery. As Sloan’s investigation unfolds, a tragic Florida cold case, local superstitions, and a shocking conspiracy collide. For Sloan, finding Stafford and uncovering the buried secrets of the past soon drag her deeper into the dark unknown than she feared. </Summary>
		<Pages> 296 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567890169 </ISBN>
		<Author> Andrew Mayne </Author>
		<Price> AED 21.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="action">
		<Title> The Secret </Title>
		<Genre> Action </Genre>
		<Summary> 1992. Eight respectable, upstanding people have been found dead across the US. These deaths look like accidents and don't appear to be connected. Until one body - the victim of a fatal fall from a hospital window - generates some unexpected attention.
						That attention comes from the Secretary of Defence, who promptly calls for an inter-agency task force to investigate. Jack Reacher is assigned as the Army's representative.
						Reacher may be an exceptional soldier, but sweeping other people's secrets under the carpet isn't part of his skill set. As he races to discover the link between these victims, and who killed them, he must navigate around the ulterior motives of his new 'partners'. And all while moving into the sight line of some of the most dangerous people he has ever encountered. </Summary>
		<Pages> 400 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567890499 </ISBN>
		<Author> Lee Child </Author>
		<Price> AED 67.97 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="action">
		<Title> The Edge </Title>
		<Genre> Action </Genre>
		<Summary> The 6:20 Man is back, dropped by his handlers into a small coastal town in Maine to solve the murder of a CIA agent who knew America’s dirtiest secrets—can Travis Devine uncover the truth before his time runs out? When CIA operative Jenny Sikwell is murdered in rural Maine, government officials have immediate concerns over national security. Her laptop and phone were full of state secrets that, in the wrong hands, endanger the lives of countless operatives. In need of someone who can solve the murder quickly and retrieve the missing information, the U.S. government knows just the chameleon they can call on. </Summary>
		<Pages> 417 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567890179 </ISBN>
		<Author> David Baldacci </Author>
		<Price> AED 127.90 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="action">
		<Title> Lone Wolf </Title>
		<Genre> Action </Genre>
		<Summary> Once a black book government assassin known as Orphan X, Evan Smoak left the program, went deep underground, and reinvented himself as someone who will go anywhere, and risk everything to help the truly desperate who have nowhere else to turn. Since then, Evan has fought international crime syndicates and drug cartels, faced down the most powerful men in the world and even brought down a President. Struggling with an unexpected personal crisis, Evan goes back to the very basics of his mission - and this time, the truly desperate is a little girl who wants him to find her missing dog. Not his usual mission, and not one Evan embraces with enthusiasm, but this unlikely, tiny job quickly explodes into his biggest mission yet. one that finds him battered between twisted AI technocrat billionaires, a mysterious female assassin who seems a mirror of himself, and personal stakes so gut-wrenching he can scarcely make sense of them. </Summary>
		<Pages> 389 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567890399 </ISBN>
		<Author> Gregg Andrew </Author>
		<Price> AED 116.11 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="action">
		<Title> Swamp Spies </Title>
		<Genre> Action </Genre>
		<Summary> Things have reached a critical point in the Middle East. Carter agreed to serve as a consultant for his old Force Recon unit but for reasons unknown to his friends and family, jumped from the command center and into the field. Now he’s MIA, and Fortune is the only one who can put together a rescue mission that has any chance of being successful. But will her skills and connections be enough?Most Sinful residents are unaware of Carter’s crisis and are going about their daily lives as they always have, including local prankster Gage Babin. Except this time, Gage’s attempt to elicit laughs leaves him on a slab in the medical examiner’s office. Everyone knows how unhealthy he was, but Fortune thinks there’s more to his death than a poorly timed prank that caused his bad heart to give out.Unfortunately, what she knows and what she can prove are two different things. And unless she can find the evidence to support her theory, someone will get away with murder. </Summary>
		<Pages> 314 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567890599 </ISBN>
		<Author> Jana Deleon </Author>
		<Price> AED 29.35 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="action">
		<Title> The Chaos Agent </Title>
		<Genre> Action </Genre>
		<Summary> Artificial intelligence leads to shockingly real danger for the Gray Man in this latest entry in the #1 New York Times bestselling series.A car accident in Japan.A drowning in Seoul.A home invasion in Boston.Someone is killing the world’s leading experts on robotics and artificial intelligence. Is it a tech company trying to eliminate the competition or is it something even more sinister?After all, artificial intelligence may be the deadliest battlefield gamechanger since the creation of gunpowder. The first nation to field weapons that can act at the speed of computer commands will rule the battlefield.It’s an irresistible lure for most, but not for the Gray Man. His quest for a quiet life has led him to Central America where he and his lover, Zoya Zakharova, have assumed new identities. With a list of enemies that  includes billionaires, terrorists, and governments, they need to keep a low profile, but the world’s deadliest assassin can’t expect to hide out forever.Eventually, they’re tracked down and offered a job by an old acquaintance of Zoya’s. </Summary>
		<Pages> 556 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567890159 </ISBN>
		<Author> Mark Greaney </Author>
		<Price> AED 110.16 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="action">
		<Title> Unnatural Death </Title>
		<Genre> Action </Genre>
		<Summary> In this thrilling new installment of Patricia Cornwell’s #1 bestselling Scarpetta series, chief medical examiner Dr. Kay Scarpetta finds herself in a Northern Virginia wilderness examining the remains of two campers wanted by federal law enforcement. The victims have been mauled beyond recognition, and other evidence is terrifying and baffling including a larger-than-life footprint. After the most frightening body retrievals of her career, Scarpetta must discover who would commit murders this savage, and why. </Summary>
		<Pages> 432 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567890699 </ISBN>
		<Author> Patricia Cornwell </Author>
		<Price> AED 55.04 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="action">
		<Title> Dark Matter </Title>
		<Genre> Action </Genre>
		<Summary> In this world he's woken up to, Jason's life is not the one he knows.
                    His wife is not his wife. His son was never born. And Jason is not an ordinary college physics professor,
                    but a celebrated genius who has achieved something remarkable. Something impossible. Is it this world or the other that's the dream?
                    And even if the home he remembers is real, how can Jason possibly make it back to the family he loves? The answers lie in a journey
                    more wondrous and horrifying than anything he could've imagined - one that will force him to confront the darkest parts of himself
                    even as he battles a terrifying, seemingly unbeatable foe. </Summary>
		<Pages> 368 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 9781101904244 </ISBN>
		<Author> Blake Crouch </Author>
		<Price> AED 59.50 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="drama">
		<Title> Malibu Rising </Title>
		<Genre> Drama </Genre>
		<Summary> Four famous siblings throw an epic party to celebrate the end of the summer. But over the course of twenty-four hours, their lives will change forever. Malibu: August, 1983. It’s the day of Nina Riva’s annual end-of-summer party, and anticipation is at a fever pitch. Everyone wants to be around the famous Rivas: Nina, the talented surfer and supermodel; brothers Jay and Hud, one a championship surfer, the other a renowned photographer; and their adored baby sister, Kit. Together, the siblings are a source of fascination in Malibu and the world over—especially as the offspring of the legendary singer, Mick Riva. The only person not looking forward to the party of the year is Nina herself, who never wanted to be the center of attention, and who has also just been very publicly abandoned by her pro tennis player husband. Oh, and maybe Hud—because it is long past time to confess something to the brother from whom he’s been inseparable since birth.</Summary>
		<Pages> 369 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567896999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Taylor Jenkins Reid </Author>
		<Price> AED 28.10 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="drama">
		<Title> The Last Letter </Title>
		<Genre> Drama </Genre>
		<Summary> Beckett, If you’re reading this, well, you know the last-letter drill. You made it. I didn’t. Get off the guilt train, because I know if there was any chance you could have saved me, you would have.
				I need one thing from you: get out of the army and get to Telluride.
				My little sister Ella’s raising the twins alone. She’s too independent and won’t accept help easily, but she has lost our grandmother, our parents, and now me. It’s too much for anyone to endure. It’s not fair.
				And here’s the kicker: there’s something else you don’t know that’s tearing her family apart. She’s going to need help.
				So if I’m gone, that means I can’t be there for Ella. I can’t help them through this. But you can. So I’m begging you, as my best friend, go take care of my sister, my family.
				Please don’t make her go through it alone. Ryan </Summary>
		<Pages> 426 </Pages>
		<ISBN> ‎123567894999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Rebecca Yarros </Author>
		<Price> AED 53.43 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="drama">
		<Title> American Dirt </Title>
		<Genre> Drama </Genre>
		<Summary> Jeanine Cummins's American Dirt, the #1 New York Times bestseller and Oprah Book Club pick that has sold over two million copies, is finally available in paperback.
				Lydia lives in Acapulco. She has a son, Luca, the love of her life, and a wonderful husband who is a journalist. And while cracks are beginning to show in Acapulco because of the cartels, Lydia’s life is, by and large, fairly comfortable. But after her husband’s tell-all profile of the newest drug lord is published, none of their lives will ever be the same.
				Forced to flee, Lydia and Luca find themselves joining the countless people trying to reach the United States. Lydia soon sees that everyone is running from something. But what exactly are they running to? </Summary>
		<Pages> 459 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567890999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Jeanine Cummins </Author>
		<Price> AED 41.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="drama">
		<Title> Magnolia Parks </Title>
		<Genre> Drama </Genre>
		<Summary> She is a beautiful, affluent, self-involved and mildly neurotic London socialite. He is Britain's most photographed bad-boy lothario who broke her heart. But Magnolia Parks and BJ Ballentine are meant to be, and everyone knows it. They're in the stars... just suspended in a strange kind of love that looks like hurting each other a lot of the time: She dates other people to keep him at bay; he sleeps with other girls to get back at her for it. But at the end of their every sad endeavour to get over one another, it's still each other they crawl back to. But their dysfunction is catching up with them, pulling at their seams and fraying the world they've built; a world where neither has to ever let the other go completely. As the cracks start to show and secrets begin to surface, Magnolia and BJ are finally forced to face the formidable question they've been avoiding all their lives: how many loves do you really get in a lifetime? </Summary>
		<Pages> 423 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567895999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Jessa Hastings </Author>
		<Price> AED 33.77 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="drama">
		<Title> Heart Bones </Title>
		<Genre> Drama </Genre>
		<Summary> Life and a dismal last name are the only two things Beyah Grim's parents ever gave her. After carving her path all on her own, Beyah is well on her way to bigger and better things, thanks to no one but herself.
				With only two short months separating her from the future she's built and the past she desperately wants to leave behind, an unexpected death leaves Beyah with no place to go during the interim. Forced to reach out to her last resort, Beyah has to spend the remainder of her summer on a peninsula in Texas with a father she barely knows. Beyah's plan is to keep her head down and let the summer slip by seamlessly, but her new neighbor Samson throws a wrench in that plan.
				Samson and Beyah have nothing in common on the surface. </Summary>
		<Pages> 338 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567892999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Colleen Hoover </Author>
		<Price> AED 28.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="drama">
		<Title> Hello Beautiful </Title>
		<Genre> Drama </Genre>
		<Summary> An emotionally layered and engrossing story of a family that asks: Can love make a broken person whole?
				William Waters grew up in a house silenced by tragedy, where his parents could hardly bear to look at him, much less love him. So it’s a relief when his skill on the basketball court earns him a scholarship to college, far away from his childhood home. He soon meets Julia Padavano, a spirited and ambitious young woman who surprises William with her appreciation of his quiet steadiness. With Julia comes her family; she is inseparable from her three younger sisters: Sylvie, the dreamer, is happiest with her nose in a book and imagines a future different from the expected path of wife and mother; Cecelia, the family’s artist; and Emeline, who patiently takes care of all of them. Happily, the Padavanos fold Julia’s new boyfriend into their loving, chaotic household. </Summary>
		<Pages> 416 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567893999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Ann Napolitano </Author>
		<Price> AED 51.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="drama">
		<Title> Until August </Title>
		<Genre> Drama </Genre>
		<Summary> The extraordinary rediscovered novel from the Nobel Prize–winning author of Love in the Time of Cholera and One Hundred Years of Solitude
				Sitting alone beside the languorous blue waters of the lagoon, Ana Magdalena Bach contemplates the men at the hotel bar. She has been happily married for twenty-seven years and has no reason to escape the life she has made with her husband and children. And yet, every August, she travels by ferry here to the island where her mother is buried, and for one night takes a new lover.
				Across sultry Caribbean evenings full of salsa and boleros, lotharios and conmen, Ana journeys further each year into the hinterland of her desire and the fear hidden in her heart.
				Constantly surprising, joyously sensual, Until August is a profound meditation on freedom, regret, self-transformation, and the mysteries of love—an unexpected gift from one of the greatest writers the world has ever known. </Summary>
		<Pages> 144 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567818999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Gabriel Garcia </Author>
		<Price> AED 53.43 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="drama">
		<Title> Apples Never Fall </Title>
		<Genre> Drama </Genre>
		<Summary> From #1 New York Times bestselling author Liane Moriarty comes a novel that looks at marriage, siblings, and how the people we love the most can hurt us the deepest
				The Delaney family love one another dearly—it’s just that sometimes they want to murder each other . . .
				If your mother was missing, would you tell the police? Even if the most obvious suspect was your father?
				This is the dilemma facing the four grown Delaney siblings.
				The Delaneys are fixtures in their community. The parents, Stan and Joy, are the envy of all of their friends. They’re killers on the tennis court, and off it their chemistry is palpable. But after fifty years of marriage, they’ve finally sold their famed tennis academy and are ready to start what should be the golden years of their lives. So why are Stan and Joy so miserable? </Summary>
		<Pages> 467 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567891999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Liane Moriarty </Author>
		<Price> AED 29.50 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="drama">
		<Title> The Stillwater Girls </Title>
		<Genre> Drama </Genre>
		<Summary> Two sisters raised in fear are about to find out why in a chilling novel of psychological suspense from the author of The Thinnest Air.
				Ignorant of civilization and cautioned against its evils, nineteen-year-old Wren and her two sisters, Sage and Evie, were raised in off-the-grid isolation in a primitive cabin in upstate New York. When the youngest grows gravely ill, their mother leaves with the child to get help from a nearby town. And they never return.
				As months pass, hope vanishes. Supplies are low. Livestock are dying. A brutal winter is bearing down. Then comes the stranger. He claims to be looking for the girls’ mother, and he’s not leaving without them. </Summary>
		<Pages> 256 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567808999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Minka Kent </Author>
		<Price> AED 23.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="drama">
		<Title> After Annie </Title>
		<Genre> Drama </Genre>
		<Summary> When Annie Brown dies suddenly, her husband, her four young children and her closest friend are left to struggle without the woman who centered their lives. Bill Brown finds himself overwhelmed, and Annie’s best friend Annemarie is lost to old bad habits without Annie’s support. It is Annie’s daughter, Ali, forced to try to care for her younger brothers and even her father, who manages to maintain some semblance of their former lives for them all, and who confronts the complicated truths of adulthood.
				Yet over the course of the next year, while Annie looms large in their memories, all three are able to grow, to change, even to become stronger and more sure of themselves. The enduring power Annie gave to those who loved her is the power to love, and to go on without her. </Summary>
		<Pages> 304 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567890899 </ISBN>
		<Author> Anna Quindlen </Author>
		<Price> AED 45.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="drama">
		<Title> The Push </Title>
		<Genre> Drama </Genre>
		<Summary> A tense, page-turning psychological drama about the making and breaking of a family–and a woman whose experience of motherhood is nothing at all what she hoped for–and everything she feared.
				Blythe Connor is determined that she will be the warm, comforting mother to her new baby Violet that she herself never had.
				But in the thick of motherhood’s exhausting early days, Blythe becomes convinced that something is wrong with her daughter–she doesn’t behave like most children do.
				Or is it all in Blythe’s head? Her husband, Fox, says she’s imagining things. The more Fox dismisses her fears, the more Blythe begins to question her own sanity, and the more we begin to question what Blythe is telling us about her life as well. </Summary>
		<Pages> 307 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567898999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Ashley Audrain </Author>
		<Price> AED 24.15 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="drama">
		<Title> The Paper Palace </Title>
		<Genre> Drama </Genre>
		<Summary> It is a perfect July morning, and Elle, a fifty-year-old happily married mother of three, awakens at "The Paper Palace"—the family summer place which she has visited every summer of her life. But this morning is different: last night Elle and her oldest friend Jonas crept out the back door into the darkness and had sex with each other for the first time, all while their spouses chatted away inside.
				Now, over the next twenty-four hours, Elle will have to decide between the life she has made with her genuinely beloved husband, Peter, and the life she always imagined she would have had with her childhood love, Jonas, if a tragic event hadn't forever changed the course of their lives. </Summary>
		<Pages> 400 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567897999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Miranda Cowley Heller </Author>
		<Price> AED 25.00 </Price>
	</book>

	<book category="fiction">
		<Title> 1984 </Title>
		<Genre> Fiction </Genre>
		<Summary> A masterpiece of rebellion and imprisonment where war is peace freedom is slavery and Big Brother is watching Thought Police Big Brother Orwellian. These words have entered our vocabulary because of George Orwell's classic dystopian novel 1984. The story of one man's nightmare odyssey as he pursues a forbidden love affair through a world ruled by warring states and a power structure that controls not only information but also individual thought and memory. 1984 is a prophetic haunting tale. More relevant than ever before 1984 exposes the worst crimes imaginable the destruction of truth freedom and individuality With a foreword by Thomas Pynchon. With a foreword by Thomas Pynchon. A masterpiece of rebellion and imprisonment where war is peace freedom is slavery and Big Brother is watching View our feature on George Orwell's 1984. This beautiful paperback edition features deckled edges and french flaps a perfect gift for any occasion. </Summary>
		<Pages> 368 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567298999 </ISBN>
		<Author> George Orwell	 </Author>
		<Price> AED 80.91 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="fiction">
		<Title> The Alchemist </Title>
		<Genre> Fiction </Genre>
		<Summary> Combining magic, mysticism, wisdom, and wonder into an inspiring tale of self-discovery, The Alchemist has become a modern classic, selling millions of copies around the world and transforming the lives of countless readers across generations.
				Paulo Coelho's masterpiece tells the mystical story of Santiago, an Andalusian shepherd boy who yearns to travel in search of a worldly treasure. His quest will lead him to riches far different—and far more satisfying—than he ever imagined. Santiago's journey teaches us about the essential wisdom of listening to our hearts, recognizing opportunity and learning to read the omens strewn along life's path, and, most importantly, following our dreams. </Summary>
		<Pages> 182 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567198999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Paulo Coelho </Author>
		<Price> AED 84.47 </Price>
	</book>

	<book category="fiction">
		<Title> The Help </Title>
		<Genre> Fiction </Genre>
		<Summary> Three ordinary women are about to take one extraordinary step.
				Twenty-two-year-old Skeeter has just returned home after graduating from Ole Miss. She may have a degree, but it is 1962, Mississippi, and her mother will not be happy till Skeeter has a ring on her finger. Skeeter would normally find solace with her beloved maid Constantine, the woman who raised her, but Constantine has disappeared and no one will tell Skeeter where she has gone.
				Aibileen is a black maid, a wise, regal woman raising her seventeenth white child. Something has shifted inside her after the loss of her own son, who died while his bosses looked the other way. She is devoted to the little girl she looks after, though she knows both their hearts may be broken.
				Minny, Aibileen's best friend, is short, fat, and perhaps the sassiest woman in Mississippi. She can cook like nobody's business, but she can't mind her tongue, so she's lost yet another job. Minny finally finds a position working for someone too new to town to know her reputation. But her new boss has secrets of her own. </Summary>
		<Pages> 464 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 	123567878999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Kathryn Stockett </Author>
		<Price> AED 71.24 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="fiction">
		<Title> Jane Eyre </Title>
		<Genre> Fiction </Genre>
		<Summary> A gothic masterpiece of tempestuous passions and dark secrets, Charlotte Brontë's Jane Eyre is edited with an introduction and notes by Stevie Davis in Penguin Classics.
				Charlotte Brontë tells the story of orphaned Jane Eyre, who grows up in the home of her heartless aunt, enduring loneliness and cruelty. This troubled childhood strengthens Jane's natural independence and spirit - which prove necessary when she finds employment as a governess to the young ward of Byronic, brooding Mr Rochester. As her feelings for Rochester develop, Jane gradually uncovers Thornfield Hall's terrible secret, forcing her to make a choice. Should she stay with Rochester and live with the consequences, or follow her convictions - even if it means leaving the man she loves? A novel of intense power and intrigue, Jane Eyre dazzled readers with its passionate depiction of a woman's search for equality and freedom. </Summary>
		<Pages> 532 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 	123567868999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Charlotte Bronte </Author>
		<Price> AED 40.40 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="fiction">
		<Title> The Kite Runner </Title>
		<Genre> Fiction </Genre>
		<Summary> 1970s Afghanistan: Twelve-year-old Amir is desperate to win the local kite-fighting tournament and his loyal friend Hassan promises to help him. But neither of the boys can foresee what would happen to Hassan that afternoon, an event that is to shatter their lives. After the Russians invade and the family is forced to flee to America, Amir realises that one day he must return to an Afghanistan under Taliban rule to find the one thing that his new world cannot grant him: redemption. </Summary>
		<Pages> 371 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 	123567858999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Khaled Hosseini </Author>
		<Price> AED 34.04 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="fiction">
		<Title> Dune </Title>
		<Genre> Fiction </Genre>
		<Summary> Set on the desert planet Arrakis, Dune is the story of the boy Paul Atreides, heir to a noble family tasked with ruling an inhospitable world where the only thing of value is the “spice” melange, a drug capable of extending life and enhancing consciousness. Coveted across the known universe, melange is a prize worth killing for...
				When House Atreides is betrayed, the destruction of Paul’s family will set the boy on a journey toward a destiny greater than he could ever have imagined. And as he evolves into the mysterious man known as Muad’Dib, he will bring to fruition humankind’s most ancient and unattainable dream. </Summary>
		<Pages> 658 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 	123567998999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Frank Herbert </Author>
		<Price> AED 48.56 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="fiction">
		<Title> Mockingjay </Title>
		<Genre> Fiction </Genre>
		<Summary> Katniss Everdeen, girl on fire, has survived, even though her home has been destroyed. Gale has escaped. Katniss's family is safe. Peeta has been captured by the Capitol. Distric 13 really does exist. There are rebels. There are new leaders. A revolution is unfolding.
				It is by design that Katniss was rescued from the arena in the cruel and haunting Quarter Quell, and it is by design that she has long been part of the revolution without knowing it. District 13 has come out of the shadows and is plotting to overthrow the Captiol. Everyone, it seems, has had a hand in the carefully laid plans - except Katniss.
				The success of the rebellion hinges on Katniss's willingness to be a pawn, to accept responsibility for countless lives, and to change the course of the future of Panem. To do this,s he must put aside her feelings of anger and distrust. She must become the rebels' Mockingjay - no matter what the personal cost. </Summary>
		<Pages> 400 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 	123567838999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Suzanne Collins </Author>
		<Price> AED 24.15 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="fiction">
		<Title> The Giver </Title>
		<Genre> Fiction </Genre>
		<Summary> The Giver is a 1993 American young adult dystopian novel written by Lois Lowry, set in a society which at first appears to be utopian but is revealed to be dystopian as the story progresses. At the age of twelve, Jonas, a young boy from a seemingly utopian, futuristic world, is singled out to receive special training from The Giver, who alone holds the memories of the true joys and pain of life.In the novel, the society has taken away pain and strife by converting to "Sameness", a plan that has also eradicated emotional depth from their lives. In an effort to preserve order, the society also lacks any color, climate, terrain, and a true sense of equality. The protagonist of the story, a 12-year-old boy named Jonas, is selected to inherit the position of Receiver of Memory, the person who stores all the memories of the time before Sameness. Jonas struggles with concepts of the new emotions and things introduced to him, and whether they are inherently good, evil, or in between, and whether it is possible to have one without the other. </Summary>
		<Pages> 208 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 	123567898999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Lois Lowry </Author>
		<Price> AED 29.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="fiction">
		<Title> Animal Farm </Title>
		<Genre> Fiction </Genre>
		<Summary> A farm is taken over by its overworked, mistreated animals. With flaming idealism and stirring slogans, they set out to create a paradise of progress, justice, and equality. Thus the stage is set for one of the most telling satiric fables ever penned –a razor-edged fairy tale for grown-ups that records the evolution from revolution against tyranny to a totalitarianism just as terrible.
				When Animal Farm was first published, Stalinist Russia was seen as its target. Today it is devastatingly clear that wherever and whenever freedom is attacked, under whatever banner, the cutting clarity and savage comedy of George Orwell’s masterpiece have a meaning and message still ferociously fresh. </Summary>
		<Pages> 141 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 	123567098999 </ISBN>
		<Author> George Orwell </Author>
		<Price> AED 10.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="fiction">
		<Title> The Martian </Title>
		<Genre> Fiction </Genre>
		<Summary> Six days ago, astronaut Mark Watney became one of the first people to walk on Mars.
				Now, he’s sure he’ll be the first person to die there.
				After a dust storm nearly kills him and forces his crew to evacuate while thinking him dead, Mark finds himself stranded and completely alone with no way to even signal Earth that he’s alive—and even if he could get word out, his supplies would be gone long before a rescue could arrive.
				Chances are, though, he won’t have time to starve to death. The damaged machinery, unforgiving environment, or plain-old “human error” are much more likely to kill him first.
				But Mark isn’t ready to give up yet. Drawing on his ingenuity, his engineering skills — and a relentless, dogged refusal to quit — he steadfastly confronts one seemingly insurmountable obstacle after the next. Will his resourcefulness be enough to overcome the impossible odds against him? </Summary>
		<Pages> 384 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 	123567848999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Andy Weir </Author>
		<Price> AED 39.16 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="fiction">
		<Title> Station Eleven </Title>
		<Genre> Fiction </Genre>
		<Summary> An audacious, darkly glittering novel set in the eerie days of civilization’s collapse—the spellbinding story of a Hollywood star, his would-be savior, and a nomadic group of actors roaming the scattered outposts of the Great Lakes region, risking everything for art and humanity.
				Kirsten Raymonde will never forget the night Arthur Leander, the famous Hollywood actor, had a heart attack on stage during a production of King Lear. That was the night when a devastating flu pandemic arrived in the city, and within weeks, civilization as we know it came to an end.
				Twenty years later, Kirsten moves between the settlements of the altered world with a small troupe of actors and musicians. They call themselves The Traveling Symphony, and they have dedicated themselves to keeping the remnants of art and humanity alive. But when they arrive in St. Deborah by the Water, they encounter a violent prophet who will threaten the tiny band’s existence. And as the story takes off, moving back and forth in time, and vividly depicting life before and after the pandemic, the strange twist of fate that connects them all will be revealed. </Summary>
		<Pages> 333 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 	123567828999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Emily St. John Mandel </Author>
		<Price> AED 65.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="fiction">
		<Title> Gone Girl </Title>
		<Genre> Fiction </Genre>
		<Summary> Who are you?
				What have we done to each other?
				These are the questions Nick Dunne finds himself asking on the morning of his fifth wedding anniversary when his wife Amy suddenly disappears. The police suspect Nick. Amy's friends reveal that she was afraid of him, that she kept secrets from him. He swears it isn't true. A police examination of his computer shows strange searches. He says they weren't made by him. And then there are the persistent calls on his mobile phone.
				So what did happen to Nick's beautiful wife? </Summary>
		<Pages> 415 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 	123567888999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Gillian Flynn </Author>
		<Price> AED 44.05 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="humour">
		<Title> Heart to Heart </Title>
		<Genre> Humour </Genre>
		<Summary> Applying to be a contestant on a reality dating show is the last thing I ever thought I would do…Well, aside from actually being on a reality dating show, that is. But here I am on Heart to Heart, hoping to come in second place.
				Yes, second place.
				I know how crazy that sounds, especially since this season’s love interest is none other than Tristan Tate, my teenage crush.  I just have to get through this reality television gig, win viewers over, and not fall for any of the contestants. If I can manage that, I’ll have my career back, provided a wrench doesn’t get thrown into the whole thing.
				Enter Avery Martin: the wrench. Avery stumbled into my life, quite literally, and I haven’t been able to get her out of my mind since then.
				And that’s a huge problem. </Summary>
		<Pages> 370 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123569798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Sara Furlong Burr </Author>
		<Price> AED 64.95 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="humour">
		<Title> Bunt! </Title>
		<Genre> Humour </Genre>
		<Summary> Molly Bauer's first year of college is not the picture-perfect piece of art she'd always envisioned. On day one at PICA, Molly discovers that—through some horrible twist of fate—her full-ride scholarship has vanished! But the ancient texts (PICA's dusty financial aid documents) reveal a loophole. If Molly and 9 other art students win a single game of softball, they'll receive a massive athletic scholarship. Can Molly's crew of ragtag artists succeed in softball without dropping the ball?
				The author of the New York Times best-selling Check, Please series, Ngozi Ukazu returns with debut artist Madeline Rupert to bring an energetic young adult story about authenticity, old vs. new, and college failure. It also poses the question: “Is art school worth it?” </Summary>
		<Pages> 288 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123563798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Ngozi Ukazu </Author>
		<Price> AED 45.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="humour">
		<Title> Buffalo Fluffalo </Title>
		<Genre> Humour </Genre>
		<Summary> Introducing a sweet and silly buffalo who tries to bluff and fluff his way into being bigger than he really is. This laugh-out-loud story by an Emmy-nominated comedy writer shows it’s okay to be yourself.
				I’m the Buffalo Fluffalo
				I heave and I huffalo
				Leave me alone because
				I’ve had enuffalo.
				Buffalo Fluffalo arrives on the scene puffed up with self-importance. Stomping around and raising billows of dust, Buffalo Fluffalo proclaims his superiority to the other creatures—the ram, the prairie dog, and the crow—who just want to be his friend. So Buffalo Fluffalo, who has had enuffalo , heads off to grumble to himself. </Summary>
		<Pages> 10 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123564798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Bess Kalb </Author>
		<Price> AED 110.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="humour">
		<Title> Really Good, Actually </Title>
		<Genre> Humour </Genre>
		<Summary> A hilarious and painfully relatable debut novel about one woman’s messy search for joy and meaning in the wake of an unexpected breakup, from comedian, essayist, and award-winning screenwriter Monica Heisey
				Maggie is fine. She’s doing really good, actually. Sure, she’s broke, her graduate thesis on something obscure is going nowhere, and her marriage only lasted 608 days, but at the ripe old age of twenty-nine, Maggie is determined to embrace her new life as a Surprisingly Young Divorcée™.
				Now she has time to take up nine hobbies, eat hamburgers at 4 am, and “get back out there” sex-wise. With the support of her tough-loving academic advisor, Merris; her newly divorced friend, Amy; and her group chat (naturally), Maggie barrels through her first year of single life, intermittently dating, occasionally waking up on the floor and asking herself tough questions along the way. </Summary>
		<Pages> 370 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567698999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Monica Heisey </Author>
		<Price> AED 45.90 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="humour">
		<Title> Subculture Vulture </Title>
		<Genre> Humour </Genre>
		<Summary> A riotous, whirlwind tour through deep American subcultures ranging from Burning Man to Alcoholics Anonymous, by the writer and comedian Moshe Kasher
				After bottoming out, being institutionalized, and getting sober all by the tender age of fifteen, Moshe Kasher found himself “What’s next?” Over the ensuing decades, he discovered the a lot.
				There was his time as a boy-king of Alcoholics Anonymous, a kind of pubescent proselytizer for other teens getting and staying sober. He was a rave promoter turned DJ turned sober ecstasy dealer in San Francisco’s techno warehouse party scene of the 1990s. For fifteen years he worked as a psychedelic security guard at Burning Man, fishing hippies out of hidden chambers they’d constructed to try to sneak into the event. As a child of deaf parents, Kasher became deeply immersed in deaf culture and sign language interpretation, translating everything from end-of-life care to horny deaf clients’ attempts to hire sex workers. He reconnects and tries to make peace with his ultra-Hasidic Jewish upbringing after the death of his father before finally settling into the comedy scene where he now makes his living. </Summary>
		<Pages> 320 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567598999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Moshe Kasher </Author>
		<Price> AED 28.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="humour">
		<Title> Swanna in Love </Title>
		<Genre> Humour </Genre>
		<Summary> Best-selling author Belle ( High Maintenance, Going Down) unleashes her first new novel in over ten years
				It's the summer of 1982 and fourteen-year-old Swanna Swain is the only one left at camp. The place is a ghost town by the time her mother Val finally shows up six hours late—stoned and radiant—in a Ford pickup driven by Borislav, her new young Russian lover. Assuming she is headed home to her air-conditioned Upper West Side apartment, Swanna and her lovable younger brother Madding are instead dragged to Vermont—to an artist colony where kids are not welcome and they are forced to sleep in the back of the truck, while Val is cozy inside the house with the Russian.
				Then Swanna meets Dennis, a handsome married father of two, at a bowling alley, and, knowing a thing or two about seduction from Judy Blume, her best friend at camp, and her own parents’ many affairs—she sets out to convince Dennis to help her. But love seldom obeys rules, and even a tough, smart, city girl like Swanna might not be able to handle falling in love.
				Best-selling novelist Jennifer Belle returns with a kind of inverse Lolita that explores adolescent desire from the girl’s point of view. In turns hilarious and wildly shocking, Swanna In Love will keep your feathers ruffled and the pages gliding by. </Summary>
		<Pages> 288 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567498999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Jennifer Belle </Author>
		<Price> AED 33.64 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="humour">
		<Title> The Lede </Title>
		<Genre> Humour </Genre>
		<Summary> A fascinating, opinionated portrait of journalism and the people who make it, told through pieces collected from the incomparable six-decade career of bestselling author and beloved New Yorker writer Calvin Trillin
				“A literary treasure.”— The Washington Times
				I’ve been writing about the press almost as long as I’ve been in the game. At some point, it occurred to me that disparate pieces from various places in various styles amounted to a picture from multiple angles of what the press has been like over the years since I became a practitioner and an observer.
				Calvin Trillin has reported serious pieces across America for The New Yorker, covered the civil rights movement in the South for Time , and written comic verse for The Nation . But one of his favorite subjects over the years—a superb fit for his unique combination of reportage and humor—has been his own professional the American press. </Summary>
		<Pages> 336 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123568798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Calvin Trillin </Author>
		<Price> AED 151.47 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="humour">
		<Title> Haunted Holiday </Title>
		<Genre> Humour </Genre>
		<Summary> Giant battle robots! Cotton candy betrayal! Blasts from the past! And the ultimate challenge to stay true to themselves and each other await Theo and Alexander in the final book in the tragic series about the Sinister-Winterbottom twins, who must solve one wretched mystery after the next.
				Trapped in Aunt Saffronia’s spectral house, Theo and Alexander must work together to escape, stop their newfound nemesis Essa and her henchman Edgaren’t, save Wil and their friends, find their parents, and maybe, just maybe, get things back to normal.
				Following the clues left behind, the twins find themselves at Siren’s Song Seaside Amusement Park. Old faces and new surprises await them in a park that was built to lure in visitors… and their secrets. </Summary>
		<Pages> 267 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123560798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Kiersten White </Author>
		<Price> AED 97.88 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="humour">
		<Title> My Dark Desire </Title>
		<Genre> Humour </Genre>
		<Summary> The task was simple.
				Sneak into Potomac’s most heavily guarded manor.
				Steal back my pendant. Slip out.
				Problem number one?
				America’s most unattainable bachelor caught me.
				Problem number two?
				He decided to keep me. As the help.
				Zachary Sun’s winter may be the coldest I’ve ever felt,
				but he makes my skin burn.
				Reserved, calculated, and savagely cruel,
				he thrives on the weaknesses of others.
				Little does he know, he just met his match.
				He may be American royalty.
				But this peasant will rise to become Queen.
				Authors’ Notes: My Dark Desire is a standalone double-grump romance between a broken billionaire and a feisty maid unafraid to fight back. It is set in the decadent Dark Prince Road world. </Summary>
		<Pages> 426 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> L.J Shen </Author>
		<Price> AED 32.09 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="humour">
		<Title> Blank </Title>
		<Genre> Humour </Genre>
		<Summary> A wife, mother, and frustrated writer faces an impossible deadline for turning her life around in a hilarious debut novel about family, friendship, success, and exhilarating self-(re)discovery. Pippa Jones is a fortyish former literary sensation who fears she will be a one-hit wonder. After the follow-up book she was almost done writing, Podlusters , had to be tossed (it ended up sharing a plot and title with superstar author Ella Rankin’s summer blockbuster!), she couldn’t write a thing. Months of staring at a blank page made her confidence vanish like a one-night stand. When she finds out that she has only five days left to finish (or rather, start ) or repay an advance she’s already spent, Pippa has a brilliantly original idea. Okay, fine, her twelve-year-old son came up with it as a joke, but Pippa and her teenage daughter approved. Pippa’s not only going to make a bold statement, but she’ll change the book world while she’s at it! Can she pull it off? </Summary>
		<Pages> 234 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567398999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Zibby Owens </Author>
		<Price> AED 20.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="humour">
		<Title> Dirty Thirty </Title>
		<Genre> Humour </Genre>
		<Summary> Stephanie Plum, Trenton’s hardest working, most underappreciated bounty hunter, is offered a freelance assignment that seems simple enough. Local jeweler Martin Rabner wants her to locate his former security guard, Andy Manley (a.k.a. Nutsy), who he is convinced stole a fortune in diamonds out of his safe. Stephanie is also looking for another troubled man, Duncan Dugan, a fugitive from justice arrested for robbing the same jewelry store on the same day.
				With her boyfriend Morelli away in Miami on police business, Stephanie is taking care of Bob, Morelli’s giant orange dog who will devour anything, from Stephanie’s stray donuts to the upholstery in her car. Morelli’s absence also means the inscrutable, irresistible security expert Ranger is front and center in Stephanie’s life when things inevitably go sideways. And he seems determined to stay there.
				To complicate matters, her best friend Lula is convinced she is being stalked by a mythological demon hell-bent on relieving her of her wardrobe. </Summary>
		<Pages> 336 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123562798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Janet Evanovich </Author>
		<Price> AED 123.59 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="humour">
		<Title> Dog Man </Title>
		<Genre> Humour </Genre>
		<Summary> Our canine superhero returns in DOG MAN: THE SCARLET SHEDDER, the suspenseful and hilarious twelfth graphic novel in the #1 worldwide bestselling series by award-winning author and illustrator Dav Pilkey!
				P.U.! Dog Man got sprayed by a skunk! After being dunked in tomato juice, the stink is gone but the scarlet red color remains. Now exiled, this spunky superhero must struggle to save the citizens who shunned him! Will the ends justify the means for Petey, who's reluctantly pulled back into a life of crime in order to help Dog Man? And who will step forward when an all-new, never-before-seen villain unleashes an army of A.I. robots? </Summary>
		<Pages> 288 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123561798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Dav Pilkey </Author>
		<Price> AED 27.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="kids">
		<Title> Waverider </Title>
		<Genre> Kids </Genre>
		<Summary> The highly anticipated, thrilling conclusion to Kazu Kibuishi's #1 New York Times bestselling series! After her confrontation with Ikol, Emily finally understands the stone's power and what she must do to defend Alledia from the shadows. As she travels to Typhon to help her mom and Navin, Prince Trellis returns to the Kingdom of the Elves to save his countrymen -- and confront the fraud who has seized power in the absence of a king. The threat of darkness follows all Stonekeepers closely, and it will take the strength of both new friends and old foes to conquer it... and survive.Waverider is the final installment to the Amulet graphic novel series by Kazu Kibuishi. The story centered on Emily and Navin Hayes as they reach a conclusion in the futile war disrupting Alledia. It was released on February 6th, 2024. </Summary>
		<Pages> 256 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123566798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Kazu Kibuishi </Author>
		<Price> AED 57.33 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="kids">
		<Title> Medusa </Title>
		<Genre> Kids </Genre>
		<Summary> From National Book Award finalist Katherine Percy Jackson meets The Troubled Girls of Dragomir Academy  in this fantastical adventure about Ava, who attends a boarding school for the descendants of Greek monsters and uncovers a terrible secret that could change the world forever. Ava Baldwin has always tried to keep her anger in check, just like her mom taught her. But when know-it-all classmate Owen King tries to speak over her yet again, Ava explodes . . . and Owen freezes, becoming totally unresponsive. Although Owen recovers, Ava's parents whisk her off to her mother’s alma mater, the Accademia del Forte, a mysterious international boarding school in Venice. There, Ava and her brother, Jax, discover that the Olympian gods founded the Accademia to teach the descendants of mythological monsters how to control their emotions and their powers and become functioning, well-adjusted members of society. But not everything at the Accademia is as it seems. After her friend Fia is almost expelled for challenging a teacher, Ava realizes the school is hiding a dangerous secret. To uncover the truth, Ava and her new friends embark on an adventure that could change the way they view history, mythology—and themselves—forever…or end their lives. </Summary>
		<Pages> 288 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123586798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Katherine Marsh </Author>
		<Price> AED 12.40 </Price>
	</book>

	<book category="kids">
		<Title> Finally Heard </Title>
		<Genre> Kids </Genre>
		<Summary> From the New York Times bestselling author of Front Desk comes the sequel to Finally Seen in which Lina struggles to separate fact from fiction on social media.
				When ten-year-old Lina Gao sees her mom’s video on social media take off, she’s captivated by the potential to be seen and heard! Maybe online she can finally find the confidence she craves. Whereas in real life she’s growing so fast, she feels like microwave popcorn, bursting out of her skin!
				With the help of her two best friends, Carla and Finn, and her little sister, Millie, Lina sets off to go viral. Except there’s a lot more to social media than Lina ever imagined. </Summary>
		<Pages> 352 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123546798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Kelly Yang </Author>
		<Price> AED 9.45 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="kids">
		<Title> Averil Offline </Title>
		<Genre> Kids </Genre>
		<Summary> A fun, fast-paced story about a girl determined to cut the cord with her helicopter parents.
				Twelve-year-old coder Averil can't do anything without her parents knowing. That’s because her mom uses the Ruby Slippers surveillance app to check where she is, who she texts, and even what she eats for lunch. Averil wonders how she’s ever going to grow up if she’s not allowed to learn from mistakes. When she learns that Ruby Slippers is about to become even more invasive, she teams up with Max, a new kid at school dealing with overbearing parents of his own. Together they figure out an almost foolproof way to ditch their parents and run away to the college campus that’s home to the quirky Ruby Slippers creator. It’s an extreme challenge just getting to meet with him—but the two kids cleverly figure out a series of puzzles and get their meeting. What they find gives them pause—and gets them thinking about the value of honesty in a new light. After all, isn’t trust at the heart of their parents' need to know? </Summary>
		<Pages> 208 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123656798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Amy Noelle Parks </Author>
		<Price> AED 23.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="kids">
		<Title> Hummingbird Season </Title>
		<Genre> Kids </Genre>
		<Summary> A poignant and necessary story about finding hope during difficult times, set in the early days of the Covid-19 pandemic.
				Archie's life--and the whole world--is turned upside down by Covid-19. Suddenly there are no more Friday night dinners out, no more going to school, no more hanging out with friends . . . no leaving the house at all.
				Even though he's inside with his family all day every day, Archie can't help but feel more alone than ever before. While everyone else seems to be adapting to their new normal just fine, it's like Archie is permanently on mute, unable to find the words to describe how he feels--and sometimes, unable to find someone who will listen. The bright spot of Archie's days at home is watching and learning about the hummingbirds that feed outside his windows. But just when it seems like this could be what brings his family together again, California experiences its worst wildfire in history, and Archie's favorite hummingbird disappears. In a time when hope is hard to hold on to, Archie must find his voice and find hope once again. </Summary>
		<Pages> 272 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123526798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Stephanie V.W Lucianovic </Author>
		<Price> AED 8.99 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="kids">
		<Title> Kitten Ninja </Title>
		<Genre> Kids </Genre>
		<Summary> Fans of comics, and heartwarming stories—not to mention cats!—will love Kitten Ninja, the origin story of the incredible Cat Ninja!
				Before Cat Ninja grew up and became Metro City’s greatest defender, he was tiny, adorable Kitten Ninja and he battled...much tinier foes. (Hey, everybody has to start somewhere, right?)
				In this spin-off prequel to the enormously popular Epic Original Cat Ninja series, our favorite feline hero takes on everything a kitten-size ninja has to battle on the way to his heroic a sun spot that won’t stay put, an irresistible ball of yarn, and—every cat’s archenemy—snow! </Summary>
		<Pages> 80 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123596798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Collen A.F. Venable </Author>
		<Price> AED 4.56 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="kids">
		<Title> Sally's New Look </Title>
		<Genre> Kids </Genre>
		<Summary> Sally is going to the groomer! Lovable pup Sally is looking a little shaggy, so her owners are taking her to the groomer. It smells like a garden and Sally sees brushes and bows galore. Then it's time for a bath. Once she's squeaky clean and blow-dried, Sally gets brushed, snipped and clipped. When her owners arrive―surprise!―everyone has fancy new hairdos! </Summary>
		<Pages> 32 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123576798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Andrew Larsen </Author>
		<Price> AED 20.23 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="kids">
		<Title> Wonka </Title>
		<Genre> Kids </Genre>
		<Summary> WONKA tells the wondrous story of how the world's greatest inventor, magician and chocolate-maker becomes the beloved Willy Wonka we know today.
				Based on the upcoming Warner Bros. Pictures movie WONKA, created by Paul King and written for film by Simon Farnaby and Paul King.
				An intoxicating mix of magic and music, mayhem and emotion, all told with fabulous heart and humour - WONKA introduces readers to a young Willy Wonka, chock-full of ideas and determined to change the world one delectable bite at a time . . . proving that the best things in life begin with a dream, and if you're lucky enough to meet Willy Wonka, anything is possible. </Summary>
		<Pages> 328 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123565798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Roald Dahl </Author>
		<Price> AED 99.78 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="kids">
		<Title> The Ickabog </Title>
		<Genre> Kids </Genre>
		<Summary> Once upon a time there was a tiny kingdom called Cornucopia, as rich in happiness as it was in gold, and famous for its food. From the delicate cream cheeses of Kurdsburg to the Hopes-of-Heaven pastries of Chouxville, each was so delicious that people wept with joy as they ate them.
				But even in this happy kingdom, a monster lurks. Legend tells of a fearsome creature living far to the north in the Marshlands... the Ickabog. Some say it breathes fire, spits poison, and roars through the mist as it carries off wayward sheep and children alike. Some say it's just a myth... </Summary>
		<Pages> 290 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123516798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> J.K. Rowling </Author>
		<Price> AED 27.09 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="kids">
		<Title> Invisible </Title>
		<Genre> Kids </Genre>
		<Summary> Emotional, moving, different... Invisible tells, through the eyes of a child, a story that could be that of any of us.
				Who hasn't ever wanted to be invisible?
				Who hasn't ever wanted to stop being one?
				The problem is that I have never managed to control that power well:
				Sometimes, when I most wanted to be invisible, that was when the most people saw me, and on the other hand, when I wanted everyone to see me, that was when my body wanted to disappear. </Summary>
		<Pages> 296 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123506798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Eloy Moreno </Author>
		<Price> AED 31.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="kids">
		<Title> Break </Title>
		<Genre> Kids </Genre>
		<Summary> Olive is less-than-excited to be spending Spring Break stuck with her dad...will she be able to make the most of her trip, or will everything break apart?
				Spring Break is full of possibilities...but not for Olive.
				This year, Olive is leaving her friends and all of their exciting vacation plans behind to visit her dad at his new apartment in the city.
				Goober is thrilled to spend a whole week with their father and has a long list of activities for their time together. Olive, on the other hand, still remembers the hurt of their dad moving halfway across the world. She would rather spend time with her friend Bree or scrolling through her new phone to keep up with everything she's missing back home than catch up with him. </Summary>
		<Pages> 224 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123556798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Kayla Miller </Author>
		<Price> AED 29.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="kids">
		<Title> Hollowpox </Title>
		<Genre> Kids </Genre>
		<Summary> Morrigan Crow and her friends have survived their first year as proud scholars of the elite Wundrous Society, helped bring down the nefarious Ghastly Market, and proven themselves loyal to Unit 919. Now Morrigan faces a new, exciting challenge: to master the mysterious Wretched Arts, and control the power that threatens to consume her.
				But a strange and frightening illness has taken hold of Nevermoor, turning infected Wunimals into mindless, vicious Unnimals on the hunt. As victims of the Hollowpox multiply, panic spreads. And with the city she loves in a state of fear, Morrigan quickly realizes it's up to her to find a cure for the Hollowpox, even if it will put her - and everyone in Nevermoor - in more danger than she ever imagined. </Summary>
		<Pages> 471 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123536798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Jessica Townsend </Author>
		<Price> AED 33.56 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="non-fiction">
		<Title> Languishing </Title>
		<Genre> Non-Fiction </Genre>
		<Summary> The Emory University sociologist who coined the term languishing—low-grade mental weariness that affects our self-esteem, relationships, and motivation—explores the rise of this phenomenon and presents a comprehensive guide to flourishing in a world that demands too much. If you’re muddling through the day in a fog, often forgetting why you walked into a room . . . 
		If you feel emotionally flattened, lacking the energy to socialize or feel joy in the small things . . . 
		If you feel an inner void—like something is missing, but you aren’t sure what . . . 
		Then this book is for you.
		Languishing—the state of mental weariness that erodes our self-esteem, motivation, and sense of meaning—can be easy to brush off as the new normal, especially since indifference is one of its symptoms.</Summary>
		<Pages> 304 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 120456798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Corey Keyes </Author>
		<Price> AED 102.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="non-fiction">
		<Title> Dead Weight </Title>
		<Genre> Non-Fiction </Genre>
		<Summary> A personal and cultural look at the dark underbelly of Western beauty standards and the lethal culture of disordered eating they've wreaked

In Dead Weight, Emmeline Clein tells the story of her own disordered eating alongside, and through, other women from history, pop culture and the girls she's known and loved. Tracing the medical and cultural history of anorexia, bulimia, binge eating disorder, and orthorexia, Clein investigates the economic conditions underpinning our eating disorder epidemic, and illuminates the ways racism and today's feminism have been complicit in propping up the thin ideal. While examining Goop, Simone Weil, pro-anorexia blogs, and the flawed logic of our current treatment methods, Clein grapples with the myriad ways disordered eating has affected her own friendships and romantic relationships.</Summary>
		<Pages> 288 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 124456798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Emmeline Clein </Author>
		<Price> AED 45.86 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="non-fiction">
		<Title> Troubled </Title>
		<Genre> Non-Fiction </Genre>
		<Summary> In this raw coming-of-age memoir, in the vein of The Short and Tragic Life of Robert Peace, The Other Wes Moore, and Someone Has Led This Child to Believe, Rob Henderson vividly recounts growing up in foster care, enlisting in the US Air Force, attending elite universities, and pioneering the concept of “luxury beliefs”—ideas and opinions that confer status on the upper class while inflicting costs on the less fortunate.

Rob Henderson was born to a drug-addicted mother and a father he never met, ultimately shuttling between ten different foster homes in California. When he was adopted into a loving family, he hoped that life would finally be stable and safe. Divorce, tragedy, poverty, and violence marked his adolescent and teen years, propelling Henderson to join the military upon completing high school.</Summary>
		<Pages> 336 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123956798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Rob Henderson </Author>
		<Price> AED 95.08 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="non-fiction">
		<Title> Splinters </Title>
		<Genre> Non-Fiction </Genre>
		<Summary> From the New York Times bestselling author of The Recovering and The Empathy Exams comes the riveting story of rebuilding a life after the end of a marriage—an exploration of motherhood, art, and new love.
 
Leslie Jamison has become one of our most beloved contemporary voices, a scribe of the real, the true, the complex. She has been compared to Joan Didion and Susan Sontag, acclaimed for her powerful thinking, deep feeling, and electric prose. But while Jamison has never shied away from challenging material—scouring her own psyche and digging into our most unanswerable questions across four books— Splinters enters a new realm.</Summary>
		<Pages> 272 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123256798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Leslie Jamison </Author>
		<Price> AED 78.69 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="non-fiction">
		<Title> All In Her Head </Title>
		<Genre> Non-Fiction </Genre>
		<Summary> The fascinating history of women’s health as it’s never been told before.

For as long as medicine has been a practice, women's bodies have been treated like objects to be practiced on: examined and ignored, idealized and sexualized, shamed, subjugated, mutilated, and dismissed. The history of women’s healthcare is a story in which women themselves have too often been voiceless—a narrative instead written from the perspective of men who styled themselves as authorities on the female of the species, yet uninformed by women’s own voices, thoughts, fears, pain and experiences. The result is a cultural and societal legacy that continues to shape the (mis)treatment and care of women. </Summary>
		<Pages> 368 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 122456798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Elizabeth Comen </Author>
		<Price> AED 7.79 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="non-fiction">
		<Title> Untamed </Title>
		<Genre> Non-Fiction </Genre>
		<Summary> Soulful and uproarious, forceful and tender, Untamed is both an intimate memoir and a galvanizing wake-up call. It is the story of how one woman learned that a responsible mother is not one who slowly dies for her children, but one who shows them how to fully live. It is the story of navigating divorce, forming a new blended family, and discovering that the brokenness or wholeness of a family depends not on its structure but on each member’s ability to bring her full self to the table. And it is the story of how each of us can begin to trust ourselves enough to set boundaries, make peace with our bodies, honor our anger and heartbreak, and unleash our truest, wildest instincts so that we become women who can finally look at ourselves and say: There She Is.</Summary>
		<Pages> 333 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123856798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Glennon Doyle </Author>
		<Price> AED 20.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="non-fiction">
		<Title> Invisible Women </Title>
		<Genre> Non-Fiction </Genre>
		<Summary> Data is fundamental to the modern world. From economic development, to healthcare, to education and public policy, we rely on numbers to allocate resources and make crucial decisions. But because so much data fails to take into account gender, because it treats men as the default and women as atypical, bias and discrimination are baked into our systems. And women pay tremendous costs for this bias, in time, money, and often with their lives.

Celebrated feminist advocate Caroline Criado Perez investigates the shocking root cause of gender inequality and research in Invisible Women​, diving into women’s lives at home, the workplace, the public square, the doctor’s office, and more. </Summary>
		<Pages> 448 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 121456798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Caroline Criado </Author>
		<Price> AED 46.57 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="non-fiction">
		<Title> Think Again </Title>
		<Genre> Non-Fiction </Genre>
		<Summary> Think Again is a book about the benefit of doubt, and about how we can get better at embracing the unknown and the joy of being wrong. Evidence has shown that creative geniuses are not attached to one identity, but constantly willing to rethink their stances and that leaders who admit they don't know something and seek critical feedback lead more productive and innovative teams.

New evidence shows us that as a mindset and a skilllset, rethinking can be taught and Grant explains how to develop the necessary qualities to do it. Section 1 explores why we struggle to think again and how we can learn to do it as individuals, arguing that 'grit' alone can actually be counterproductive. Section 2 discusses how we can help others think again through learning about 'argument literacy'. And the final section 3 looks at how schools, businesses and governments fall short in building cultures that encourage rethinking.</Summary>
		<Pages> 307 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123056798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Adam Grant </Author>
		<Price> AED 45.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="non-fiction">
		<Title> Vanderbilt </Title>
		<Genre> Non-Fiction </Genre>
		<Summary> New York Times bestselling author and journalist Anderson Cooper teams with New York Times bestselling historian and novelist Katherine Howe to chronicle the rise and fall of a legendary American dynasty—his mother’s family, the Vanderbilts.

When eleven-year-old Cornelius Vanderbilt began to work on his father’s small boat ferrying supplies in New York Harbor at the beginning of the nineteenth century, no one could have imagined that one day he would, through ruthlessness, cunning, and a pathological desire for money, build two empires—one in shipping and another in railroads—that would make him the richest man in America. His staggering fortune was fought over by his heirs after his death in 1877, sowing familial discord that would never fully heal.</Summary>
		<Pages> 317 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123756798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Anderson Cooper </Author>
		<Price> AED 131.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="non-fiction">
		<Title> Supercommunicators </Title>
		<Genre> Non-Fiction </Genre>
		<Summary> From the New York Times bestselling author of The Power of Habit, a fascinating exploration of what makes conversations work, and how we can all learn to be supercommunicators at work and in life.

Come inside a jury room as one juror leads a starkly divided room to consensus. Join a young CIA officer as he recruits a reluctant foreign agent. And sit with an accomplished surgeon as he tries, and fails, to convince yet another cancer patient to opt for the less risky course of treatment. In Supercommunicators, Charles Duhigg blends deep research and his trademark storytelling skills to show how we can all learn to identify and leverage the hidden layers that lurk beneath every conversation.

Communication is a superpower.</Summary>
		<Pages> 320 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123156798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Charles Duhigg </Author>
		<Price> AED 89.64 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="non-fiction">
		<Title> Relinquished </Title>
		<Genre> Non-Fiction </Genre>
		<Summary> A powerful decade-long study of adoption in the age of Roe, revealing the grief of the American mothers for whom the choice to parent was never real

Adoption has always been viewed as a beloved institution for building families, as well as a mutually agreeable common ground in the abortion debate, but little attention has been paid to the lives of mothers who relinquish infants for private adoption. Relinquished reveals adoption to be a path of constrained choice for those for whom abortion is inaccessible, or for whom parenthood is untenable. The stories of relinquishing mothers are stories about our country's refusal to care for families at the most basic level, and to instead embrace an individual, private solution to a large-scale, social problem.

With the recent decision in Dobbs v. Jackson Women's Health Organization revoking abortion protections and the upcoming decision in Brackeen v. Haaland likely to revoke the Indian Child Welfare Act, we are in a political moment in which adoption is, increasingly, being revealed as an institution devoted to separating families and policing parenthood under the guise of feel-good family-building.</Summary>
		<Pages> 311 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123356798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Gretchen Sisson </Author>
		<Price> AED 72.84 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="non-fiction">
		<Title> Practical Optimism </Title>
		<Genre> Non-Fiction </Genre>
		<Summary> A practical program rooted in optimism to help you live fully and joyfully in an imperfect, turbulent world

As the first medical director and attending psychiatrist at the World Trade Center Mental Health Program, Dr. Sue Varma worked directly with civilian and first-responder survivors in the aftermath of 9/11. There, she met people at every point of the stress and trauma continuum. She saw devastation and stagnancy as much as she saw amazing resilience and growth. She asked how do some people survive, even thrive, despite profound challenges? And how can we optimize the things we have control over, while buffering ourselves from stress?

Through her work with patients and combining philosophy, her own personal experience, and a review of the latest research in psychology, psychiatry, medicine, and neuroscience, Dr. Varma discovered that the answer lies in cultivating an optimistic mindset that stays tethered to the real world and helps us make sound and reasonable decisions.</Summary>
		<Pages> 336 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123456798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Sue Varma </Author>
		<Price> AED 60.33 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="romance">
		<Title> The Catch </Title>
		<Genre> Romance </Genre>
		<Summary> A grumpy lobster fisherman tosses a fashion influencer’s impeccably curated life overboard in the next romantic comedy from international bestselling author Amy Lea.

In a last-ditch effort to rescue her brand from the brink of irrelevance, Boston fashion influencer Melanie Karlsen finds herself in a rural fishing village on the east coast of Canada. The only thing scarier than nature itself? The burly and bearded bed-and-breakfast owner and fisherman, Evan Whaler—who single-handedly disproves the theory that Canadians are “nice.”

After a boating accident lands Evan unconscious in the hospital, Mel is mistaken for his fiancée by his welcoming yet quirky family, who are embroiled in a long-standing feud over the B and B. In a bold attempt to mend family fences, Mel agrees to fake their engagement for one week in exchange for Evan’s help with her social media content. </Summary>
		<Pages> 416 </Pages>
		<ISBN> ‎‎‎123567890121 </ISBN>
		<Author> Amy Lea </Author>
		<Price> AED 44.42 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="romance">
		<Title> Fangirl Down </Title>
		<Genre> Romance </Genre>
		<Summary> #1 New York Times bestselling author Tessa Bailey launches a super sexy sports romance series with a rom-com about a bad boy professional athlete who falls for his biggest fan...

Wells Whitaker was once golf’s hottest rising star, but lately, all he has to show for his “promising” career is a killer hangover, a collection of broken clubs, and one remaining supporter. No matter how bad he plays, the beautiful, sunny redhead is always on the sidelines. He curses, she cheers. He scowls, she smiles. But when Wells quits in a blaze of glory and his fangirl finally goes home, he knows he made the greatest mistake of his life.

Josephine Doyle believed in the gorgeous, grumpy golfer, even when he didn’t believe in himself. Yet after he throws in the towel, she begins to wonder if her faith was misplaced. Then a determined Wells shows up at her door with a wild proposal: be his new caddy, help him turn his game around, and split the prize money. And considering Josephine’s professional and personal life is in shambles, she could really use the cash… </Summary>
		<Pages> 380 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567890122 </ISBN>
		<Author> Tessa Bailey </Author>
		<Price> AED 10.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="romance">
		<Title> Heartless Hunter </Title>
		<Genre> Romance </Genre>
		<Summary> On the night Rune’s life changed forever, blood ran in the streets. Now, in the aftermath of a devastating revolution, witches have been diminished from powerful rulers to outcasts ruthlessly hunted due to their waning magic, and Rune must hide what she is.

Spending her days pretending to be nothing more than a vapid young socialite, Rune spends her nights as the Crimson Moth, a witch vigilante who rescues her kind from being purged. When a rescue goes wrong, she decides to throw the witch hunters off her scent and gain the intel she desperately needs by courting the handsome Gideon Sharpe - a notorious and unforgiving witch hunter loyal to the revolution - who she can't help but find herself falling for.

Gideon loathes the decadence and superficiality Rune represents, but when he learns the Crimson Moth has been using Rune’s merchant ships to smuggle renegade witches out of the republic, he inserts himself into her social circles by pretending to court her right back. </Summary>
		<Pages> 416 </Pages>
		<ISBN> ‎123567890126 </ISBN>
		<Author> Kristen Ciccarelli </Author>
		<Price> AED 90.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="romance">
		<Title> Ready or Not </Title>
		<Genre> Romance </Genre>
		<Summary> A surprise pregnancy leads to even more life-changing revelations in this heartfelt, slow-burn, friends-to-lovers romance of found family and unexpected love.

Eve Hatch is pretty content with her life. Her apartment in Brooklyn is cozy and close to her childhood best friend Willa, but far from her midwestern, traditional family who never really understood her. While her job is only dream- adjacent , she’s hoping her passion and hard work will soon help her land a more glamorous role. And sure, her most recent romantic history has consisted of not one but two disappointing men named Derek. At least she always knows what to expect…until she finds herself expecting after an uncharacteristic one-night stand.

The unplanned pregnancy cracks open all the relationships in her life. Eve's loyal friendship with Willa is feeling off , right when she needs her most. And it’s Willa’s steadfast older brother, Shep, who steps up to help. </Summary>
		<Pages> 400 </Pages>
		<ISBN> ‎123567890128 </ISBN>
		<Author> Cara Bastone </Author>
		<Price> AED 129.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="romance">
		<Title> Girl Abroad </Title>
		<Genre> Romance </Genre>
		<Summary> New York Times bestselling author Elle Kennedy brings her signature angst, drama, and humour to a new standalone romance.

When nineteen-year-old Abbey Bly gets the opportunity to study abroad for a year in London, it's the perfect chance to finally slip out from under the thumb of her beloved but overbearing retired rock star father. She's ready to be free, to discover herself - but first off, to meet the girls she's rooming with. That is, until she arrives at her gorgeous new flat to discover those roommates are actually all boys. Charming, funny, insufferably attractive boys. And off-limits, with a rule against fraternizing between housemates after unwanted drama with the previous girl.

Abbey has never considered herself a rulebreaker. But soon, she's lying to her father about her living situation and falling for not one, but two men she can't have: her rugby-player roommate and a broody musician with a girlfriend. Not to mention, her research for school has gotten her tangled in a deeply hidden scandal of a high nobility family, surrounding her in secrets on all sides. </Summary>
		<Pages> 432 </Pages>
		<ISBN> ‎123567890124 </ISBN>
		<Author> Elle Kennedy </Author>
		<Price> AED 12.74 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="romance">
		<Title> Fate Breaker </Title>
		<Genre> Romance </Genre>
		<Summary> A dark fate descends. A shattered alliance must rise.

The Companions are torn apart and the realm hangs in the balance, at the edge of ruin. Taristan and Queen Erida rise triumphant from the battlefield, while Corayne barely escapes with her life; her Companions left behind to uncertain fates.

But not all hope was lost: Corayne managed to steal Taristan's Spindleblade. Without it, Taristan can’t rip open any more Spindles. Without it, he can’t end the world.

Now, from every corner of the realm, the Companions race to reunite while they rally old allies and seek unexpected new ones, in one final push against darkness. </Summary>
		<Pages> 625 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567890123 </ISBN>
		<Author> Victoria Aveyard </Author>
		<Price> AED 54.83 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="romance">
		<Title> Happy Place </Title>
		<Genre> Romance </Genre>
		<Summary> Harriet and Wyn have been the perfect couple since they met in college—they go together like salt and pepper, honey and tea, lobster and rolls. Except, now—for reasons they’re still not discussing—they don’t.

They broke up six months ago. And still haven’t told their best friends.

Which is how they find themselves sharing the largest bedroom at the Maine cottage that has been their friend group’s yearly getaway for the last decade. Their annual respite from the world, where for one vibrant, blue week they leave behind their daily lives; have copious amounts of cheese, wine, and seafood; and soak up the salty coastal air with the people who understand them most.

Only this year, Harriet and Wyn are lying through their teeth while trying not to notice how desperately they still want each other. Because the cottage is for sale and this is the last week they’ll all have together in this place. They can’t stand to break their friends’ hearts, and so they’ll play their parts. </Summary>
		<Pages> 400 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567890125 </ISBN>
		<Author> Emily Henry </Author>
		<Price> AED 81.24 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="romance">
		<Title> Yours Truly </Title>
		<Genre> Romance </Genre>
		<Summary> A novel of terrible first impressions, hilarious second chances, and the joy in finding your perfect match.

Dr. Briana Ortiz’s life is seriously flatlining. Her divorce is just about finalized, her brother’s running out of time to find a kidney donor, and that promotion she wants? Oh, that’s probably going to the new man-doctor who’s already registering eighty-friggin’-seven on Briana’s “pain in my ass” scale. But just when all systems are set to hate, Dr. Jacob Maddox completely flips the game . . . by sending Briana a letter.

And it’s a really good letter. Like the kind that proves that Jacob isn’t actually Satan. Worse, he might be this fantastically funny and subversively likeable guy who’s terrible at first impressions. Because suddenly he and Bri are exchanging letters, sharing lunch dates in her “sob closet,” and discussing the merits of freakishly tiny horses. But when Jacob decides to give Briana the best gift imaginable—a kidney for her brother. </Summary>
		<Pages> 416 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567890139 </ISBN>
		<Author> Abby Jimenz </Author>
		<Price> AED 29.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="romance">
		<Title> Regretting You </Title>
		<Genre> Romance </Genre>
		<Summary> Morgan Grant and her sixteen-year-old daughter, Clara, would like nothing more than to be nothing alike.

Morgan is determined to prevent her daughter from making the same mistakes she did. By getting pregnant and married way too young, Morgan put her own dreams on hold. Clara doesn’t want to follow in her mother’s footsteps. Her predictable mother doesn’t have a spontaneous bone in her body.

With warring personalities and conflicting goals, Morgan and Clara find it increasingly difficult to coexist. The only person who can bring peace to the household is Chris—Morgan’s husband, Clara’s father, and the family anchor. But that peace is shattered when Chris is involved in a tragic and questionable accident. The heartbreaking and long-lasting consequences will reach far beyond just Morgan and Clara. </Summary>
		<Pages> 363 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 123567890129 </ISBN>
		<Author> Colleen Hoover </Author>
		<Price> AED 35.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="romance">
		<Title> Powerless </Title>
		<Genre> Romance </Genre>
		<Summary> She is the very thing he’s spent his whole life hunting.
He is the very thing she’s spent her whole life pretending to be.

Only the extraordinary belong in the kingdom of Ilya—the exceptional, the empowered, the Elites.

The powers these Elites have possessed for decades were graciously gifted to them by the Plague, though not all were fortunate enough to both survive the sickness and reap the reward. Those born Ordinary are just that—ordinary. And when the king decreed that all Ordinaries be banished in order to preserve his Elite society, lacking an ability suddenly became a crime—making Paedyn Gray a felon by fate and a thief by necessity.

Surviving in the slums as an Ordinary is no simple task, and Paedyn knows this better than most. Having been trained by her father to be overly observant since she was a child, Paedyn poses as a Psychic in the crowded city, blending in with the Elites as best she can in order to stay alive and out of trouble. Easier said than done.She is the very thing he’s spent his whole life hunting.
He is the very thing she’s spent her whole life pretending to be. </Summary>
		<Pages> 523 </Pages>
		<ISBN> ‎123567890127 </ISBN>
		<Author> Lauren Roberts </Author>
		<Price> AED 48.59 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="romance">
		<Title> The Unhoneymooners </Title>
		<Genre> Romance </Genre>
		<Summary> Olive is always unlucky: in her career, in love, in…well, everything. Her identical twin sister Ami, on the other hand, is probably the luckiest person in the world. Her meet-cute with her fiancé is something out of a romantic comedy (gag) and she’s managed to finance her entire wedding by winning a series of Internet contests (double gag). Worst of all, she’s forcing Olive to spend the day with her sworn enemy, Ethan, who just happens to be the best man.

Olive braces herself to get through 24 hours of wedding hell before she can return to her comfortable, unlucky life. But when the entire wedding party gets food poisoning from eating bad shellfish, the only people who aren’t affected are Olive and Ethan. And now there’s an all-expenses-paid honeymoon in Hawaii up for grabs.

Putting their mutual hatred aside for the sake of a free vacation, Olive and Ethan head for paradise, determined to avoid each other at all costs. But when Olive runs into her future boss, the little white lie she tells him is suddenly at risk to become a whole lot bigger. She and Ethan now have to pretend to be loving newlyweds, and her luck seems worse than ever. But the weird thing is that she doesn’t mind playing pretend. In fact, she feels kind of... lucky. </Summary>
		<Pages> 432 </Pages>
		<ISBN> ‎123567890119 </ISBN>
		<Author> Christina Lauren </Author>
		<Price> AED 52.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="romance">
		<Title> Tom Lake </Title>
		<Genre> Romance </Genre>
		<Summary> In this beautiful and moving novel about family, love, and growing up, Ann Patchett once again proves herself one of America’s finest writers.

In the spring of 2020, Lara’s three daughters return to the family's orchard in Northern Michigan. While picking cherries, they beg their mother to tell them the story of Peter Duke, a famous actor with whom she shared both a stage and a romance years before at a theater company called Tom Lake. As Lara recalls the past, her daughters examine their own lives and relationship with their mother, and are forced to reconsider the world and everything they thought they knew.

Tom Lake is a meditation on youthful love, married love, and the lives parents have led before their children were born. Both hopeful and elegiac, it explores what it means to be happy even when the world is falling apart. As in all of her novels, Ann Patchett combines compelling narrative artistry with piercing insights into family dynamics. The result is a rich and luminous story, told with profound intelligence and emotional subtlety, that demonstrates once again why she is one of the most revered and acclaimed literary talents working today. </Summary>
		<Pages> 309 </Pages>
		<ISBN> ‎123567890120 </ISBN>
		<Author> Ann Patchett </Author>
		<Price> AED 25.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="thriller">
		<Title> Jaded </Title>
		<Genre> Thriller </Genre>
		<Summary> A young lawyer wakes up the morning after a work gala with no memory of how she got home the previous night and must figure out what, exactly, happened—and how much she's willing to put up with to make her way to the top of the corporate ladder.

Jade isn’t even my real name. Jade began as my Starbucks name, because all children of immigrants have a Starbucks name.

Jade has become everything she ever wanted to be.

Successful lawyer.
Dutiful daughter.
Beloved girlfriend.
Loyal friend.

Until Jade wakes up the morning after a work event, naked and alone, with no idea how she got home. Caught between her parents who can’t understand, her boyfriend who feels betrayed, and her job that expects silence, the world Jade has constructed starts to crumble.

Jade thought she was everything she ever wanted to be. But now she feels like nothing at all. </Summary>
		<Pages> 384 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 129456798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Ela Lee </Author>
		<Price> AED 56.88 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="thriller">
		<Title> The Inmate </Title>
		<Genre> Thriller </Genre>
		<Summary> There are three rules Brooke Sullivan must follow as a new nurse practitioner at a men's maximum-security 1) Treat all prisoners with respect. 2) Never reveal any personal information. 3) Never EVER become too friendly with the inmates. But none of the staff at the prison knows Brooke has already broken the rules. Nobody knows about her intimate connection to Shane Nelson, one of the penitentiary's most notorious and dangerous inmates. And they certainly don't know that Shane was Brooke's high school sweetheart―the star quarterback who is now spending the rest of his life in prison for a series of grisly murders. Or that Brooke's testimony was what put him there. But Shane knows. And he will never forget. </Summary>
		<Pages> 388 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 220456798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Freida McFadden </Author>
		<Price> AED 58.09 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="thriller">
		<Title> The Guest </Title>
		<Genre> Thriller </Genre>
		<Summary> New York Times bestselling author B. A. Paris captivated psychological thriller readers everywhere with Behind Closed Doors. Now she invites you into another home full of heart-pounding secrets, in The Guest.

Some secrets never leave.

Iris and Gabriel have just arrived home from a make-or-break holiday. But a shock awaits them. One of their closest friends, Laure, is in their house. The atmosphere quickly becomes tense as she oversteps again and sleeping in their bed, wearing Iris' clothes, even rearranging the furniture.

Laure has walked out on her husband—and their good friend—Pierre, over his confession of an affair and a secret child. Iris and Gabriel want to be supportive of their friends, but as Laure's mood becomes increasingly unpredictable, her presence takes its toll.

Iris and Gabriel's only respite comes in the form of a couple new to town. But with them comes their gardener, who has a checkered past. Soon, secrets from all their pasts will unravel, some more dangerous than they could have known. </Summary>
		<Pages> 308 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 330456798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> B.A. Paris </Author>
		<Price> AED 44.77 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="thriller">
		<Title> Too Late </Title>
		<Genre> Thriller </Genre>
		<Summary> A psychological suspense novel of obsession and dangerous love. The definitive edition of Too Late from the #1 New York Times bestselling author of Verity .

Sloan will go through hell and back for those she loves. And she does so, every single day. Caught up with the alluring Asa Jackson, a notorious drug trafficker, Sloan has finally found a lifeline to cling to, even if it’s meant compromising her morals. She was in dire straits trying to pay for her brother’s care until she met Asa. But as Sloan became emotionally and economically reliant on him, he in turn developed a disturbing obsession with her—one that becomes increasingly dangerous every day.

When undercover DEA agent Carter enters the picture, Sloan’s surprised to feel an immediate attraction between them, despite knowing that if Asa finds out, he will kill him. And Asa has always been a step ahead of everyone in his life, including Sloan. No one has ever gotten in his way. </Summary>
		<Pages> 370 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 430456798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Colleen Hoover </Author>
		<Price> AED 45.58 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="thriller">
		<Title> Lone Wolf </Title>
		<Genre> Thriller </Genre>
		<Summary> Once a black book government assassin known as Orphan X, Evan Smoak left the program, went deep underground, and reinvented himself as someone who will go anywhere, and risk everything to help the truly desperate who have nowhere else to turn. Since then, Evan has fought international crime syndicates and drug cartels, faced down the most powerful men in the world and even brought down a President. Struggling with an unexpected personal crisis, Evan goes back to the very basics of his mission - and this time, the truly desperate is a little girl who wants him to find her missing dog.

Not his usual mission, and not one Evan embraces with enthusiasm, but this unlikely, tiny job quickly explodes into his biggest mission yet. one that finds him battered between twisted AI technocrat billionaires, a mysterious female assassin who seems a mirror of himself, and personal stakes so gut-wrenching he can scarcely make sense of them. </Summary>
		<Pages> 389 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 530456798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Gregg Hurwitz </Author>
		<Price> AED 46.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="thriller">
		<Title> Never Lie </Title>
		<Genre> Thriller </Genre>
		<Summary> Newlyweds Tricia and Ethan are searching for the house of their dreams.

But when they visit the remote manor that once belonged to Dr. Adrienne Hale, a renowned psychiatrist who vanished without a trace four years earlier, a violent winter storm traps them at the estate… with no chance of escape until the blizzard comes to an end.

In search of a book to keep her entertained until the snow abates, Tricia happens upon a secret room. One that contains audio transcripts from every single patient Dr. Hale has ever interviewed. As Tricia listens to the cassette tapes, she learns about the terrifying chain of events leading up to Dr. Hale’s mysterious disappearance.

Tricia plays the tapes one by one, late into the night. With each one, another shocking piece of the puzzle falls into place, and Dr. Adrienne Hale’s web of lies slowly unravels. </Summary>
		<Pages> 286 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 630456798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Freida McFadden </Author>
		<Price> AED 79.64 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="thriller">
		<Title> Ward D </Title>
		<Genre> Thriller </Genre>
		<Summary> Medical student Amy Brenner is spending the night on a locked psychiatric ward.

Amy has been dreading her evening working on Ward D, the hospital’s inpatient mental health unit. There are very specific reasons why she never wanted to do this required overnight rotation. Reasons nobody can ever find out.

And as the hours tick by, Amy grows increasingly convinced something terrible is happening within these tightly secured walls. When patients and staff start to vanish without a trace, it becomes clear that everyone on the unit is in grave danger.

Amy’s worst nightmare was spending the night on Ward D.

And now she might never escape. </Summary>
		<Pages> 333 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 730456798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Freida McFadden </Author>
		<Price> AED 23.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="thriller">
		<Title> The Coworker </Title>
		<Genre> Thriller </Genre>
		<Summary> Two women. An office filled with secrets. One terrible crime that can't be taken back

Dawn Schiff is strange. At least, everyone thinks so at Vixed, the nutritional supplement company where Dawn works as an accountant. She never says the right thing. She has no friends. And she is always at her desk at precisely 8:45 a.m.

So when Dawn doesn't show up to the office one morning, her coworker Natalie Farrell—beautiful, popular, top sales rep five years running—is surprised. Then she receives an unsettling, anonymous phone call that changes everything…

It turns out Dawn wasn't just an awkward outsider—she was being targeted by someone close. And now Natalie is irrevocably tied to Dawn as she finds herself caught in a twisted game of cat and mouse that leaves her wondering: who's the real victim? </Summary>
		<Pages> 362 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 830456798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Freida McFadden </Author>
		<Price> AED 31.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="thriller">
		<Title> The Rumor Game </Title>
		<Genre> Thriller </Genre>
		<Summary> Reporter Anne Lemire writes the Rumor Clinic, a newspaper column that disproves the many harmful rumors floating around town, some of them spread by Axis spies and others just gossip mixed with fear and ignorance. Tired of chasing silly rumors about Rosie Riveters' safety on the job, she wants to write about something bigger.

Special Agent Devon Mulvey, one of the few Catholics at the FBI, spends his weekdays preventing industrial sabotage and his Sundays spying on clerics with suspect loyalties—and he spends his evenings wooing the many lonely women whose husbands are off at war.

When Anne’s story about Nazi propaganda intersects with Devon’s investigation into the death of a factory worker, the two are led down a dangerous trail of espionage, organized crime, and domestic fascism—one that implicates their own tangled pasts and threatens to engulf the city in violence. </Summary>
		<Pages> 368 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 930456798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Thomas Mullen </Author>
		<Price> AED 52.10 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="thriller">
		<Title> The Split </Title>
		<Genre> Thriller </Genre>
		<Summary> Jane Connor is resigned to being the “plain Jane” of her family—pragmatic and dependable—so unlike her beautiful and impetuous younger sister Esme. When Esme calls Jane during a flash summer storm, announcing she’s left her high-society husband, Jane is shocked to learn her sister wishes to stay with her. Could this be an opportunity for them to become close again? The only catch: Esme needs a ride from the city to their small Connecticut hometown, and Jane is terrified of getting on the highway because of what she did when they were teens. Jane must either let Esme stand on her own two feet for once or jump to her flighty younger sister’s rescue—and her choice cleaves her life in two.

With a rollicking pace and shocking twists and turns, The Split captivatingly explores how little we know the ones we love—and how one small choice can change everything. </Summary>
		<Pages> 288 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 330056798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Kit Frick </Author>
		<Price> 54.00 AED </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="thriller">
		<Title> Salem's Cipher </Title>
		<Genre> Thriller </Genre>
		<Summary> A brilliant code breaker shatters a centuries-old conspiracy and unravels her own family secrets in an addictive and heart-pounding thriller by Edgar Award–nominated author Jess Lourey.

Salem Wiley is a genius cryptanalyst. She’s also a loner who prefers a safe and familiar path. Until her mother disappears in the wake of a brutal murder, leaving behind a cryptic warning of threats to come. Forced out of her safe zone, Salem embarks with her best friend, Bel, on a dangerous quest that reaches back centuries into America’s hidden history.

Drawn into a labyrinth of messages encrypted by Emily Dickinson and hidden in the legendary Beale Cipher, Salem discovers her mother’s double life—and the truth. An ancient and ruthless society is hell-bent on ruling the world, and only a select group of hunted women stands in its way. </Summary>
		<Pages> 412 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 330456008999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Jess Lourey </Author>
		<Price> AED 23.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book category="thriller">
		<Title> Day One </Title>
		<Genre> Thriller </Genre>
		<Summary> Marty seems to do no wrong. Trent can’t seem to get things right. When they are thrown together by tragedy, their futures may be defined by one What really happened on Day One?

Stonesmere is an English seaside suburb defined by poignant traditions passed from generation to generation, and the bonds of small town community spirit. But when a lone gunman disrupts a school assembly, he sets of a chain of events that throws this close-kint town into turmoil.

Marty is a golden girl, albeit one sometimes in the shadow of her father’s accomplishments and the care of her mother—an outsider who became a beloved teacher. Meanwhile, Trent’s home life is in the only child of a mother forever on the lookout for the boyfriend who can remake their lives, Trent longs for Stonesmere’s stability. But he and his mother only pass through. </Summary>
		<Pages> 368 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 330256798109 </ISBN>
		<Author> Abigail Dean </Author>
		<Price> AED 40.00 </Price>
	</book>
</library>
