<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../XML-XSL-DTD/Thriller.xsl"?>
<!DOCTYPE note SYSTEM "books.dtd">

<library>
	<book>
		<Title> Jaded </Title>
		<Summary> A young lawyer wakes up the morning after a work gala with no memory of how she got home the previous night and must figure out what, exactly, happened—and how much she's willing to put up with to make her way to the top of the corporate ladder.

Jade isn’t even my real name. Jade began as my Starbucks name, because all children of immigrants have a Starbucks name.

Jade has become everything she ever wanted to be.

Successful lawyer.
Dutiful daughter.
Beloved girlfriend.
Loyal friend.

Until Jade wakes up the morning after a work event, naked and alone, with no idea how she got home. Caught between her parents who can’t understand, her boyfriend who feels betrayed, and her job that expects silence, the world Jade has constructed starts to crumble.

Jade thought she was everything she ever wanted to be. But now she feels like nothing at all. </Summary>
		<Pages> 384 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 129456798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Ela Lee </Author>
		<Price> AED 56.88 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> The Inmate </Title>
		<Summary> There are three rules Brooke Sullivan must follow as a new nurse practitioner at a men's maximum-security 1) Treat all prisoners with respect. 2) Never reveal any personal information. 3) Never EVER become too friendly with the inmates. But none of the staff at the prison knows Brooke has already broken the rules. Nobody knows about her intimate connection to Shane Nelson, one of the penitentiary's most notorious and dangerous inmates. And they certainly don't know that Shane was Brooke's high school sweetheart―the star quarterback who is now spending the rest of his life in prison for a series of grisly murders. Or that Brooke's testimony was what put him there. But Shane knows. And he will never forget. </Summary>
		<Pages> 388 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 220456798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Freida McFadden </Author>
		<Price> AED 58.09 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> The Guest </Title>
		<Summary> New York Times bestselling author B. A. Paris captivated psychological thriller readers everywhere with Behind Closed Doors. Now she invites you into another home full of heart-pounding secrets, in The Guest.

Some secrets never leave.

Iris and Gabriel have just arrived home from a make-or-break holiday. But a shock awaits them. One of their closest friends, Laure, is in their house. The atmosphere quickly becomes tense as she oversteps again and sleeping in their bed, wearing Iris' clothes, even rearranging the furniture.

Laure has walked out on her husband—and their good friend—Pierre, over his confession of an affair and a secret child. Iris and Gabriel want to be supportive of their friends, but as Laure's mood becomes increasingly unpredictable, her presence takes its toll.

Iris and Gabriel's only respite comes in the form of a couple new to town. But with them comes their gardener, who has a checkered past. Soon, secrets from all their pasts will unravel, some more dangerous than they could have known. </Summary>
		<Pages> 308 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 330456798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> B.A. Paris </Author>
		<Price> AED 44.77 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Too Late </Title>
		<Summary> A psychological suspense novel of obsession and dangerous love. The definitive edition of Too Late from the #1 New York Times bestselling author of Verity .

Sloan will go through hell and back for those she loves. And she does so, every single day. Caught up with the alluring Asa Jackson, a notorious drug trafficker, Sloan has finally found a lifeline to cling to, even if it’s meant compromising her morals. She was in dire straits trying to pay for her brother’s care until she met Asa. But as Sloan became emotionally and economically reliant on him, he in turn developed a disturbing obsession with her—one that becomes increasingly dangerous every day.

When undercover DEA agent Carter enters the picture, Sloan’s surprised to feel an immediate attraction between them, despite knowing that if Asa finds out, he will kill him. And Asa has always been a step ahead of everyone in his life, including Sloan. No one has ever gotten in his way. </Summary>
		<Pages> 370 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 430456798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Colleen Hoover </Author>
		<Price> AED 45.58 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Lone Wolf </Title>
		<Summary> Once a black book government assassin known as Orphan X, Evan Smoak left the program, went deep underground, and reinvented himself as someone who will go anywhere, and risk everything to help the truly desperate who have nowhere else to turn. Since then, Evan has fought international crime syndicates and drug cartels, faced down the most powerful men in the world and even brought down a President. Struggling with an unexpected personal crisis, Evan goes back to the very basics of his mission - and this time, the truly desperate is a little girl who wants him to find her missing dog.

Not his usual mission, and not one Evan embraces with enthusiasm, but this unlikely, tiny job quickly explodes into his biggest mission yet. one that finds him battered between twisted AI technocrat billionaires, a mysterious female assassin who seems a mirror of himself, and personal stakes so gut-wrenching he can scarcely make sense of them. </Summary>
		<Pages> 389 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 530456798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Gregg Hurwitz </Author>
		<Price> AED 46.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Never Lie </Title>
		<Summary> Newlyweds Tricia and Ethan are searching for the house of their dreams.

But when they visit the remote manor that once belonged to Dr. Adrienne Hale, a renowned psychiatrist who vanished without a trace four years earlier, a violent winter storm traps them at the estate… with no chance of escape until the blizzard comes to an end.

In search of a book to keep her entertained until the snow abates, Tricia happens upon a secret room. One that contains audio transcripts from every single patient Dr. Hale has ever interviewed. As Tricia listens to the cassette tapes, she learns about the terrifying chain of events leading up to Dr. Hale’s mysterious disappearance.

Tricia plays the tapes one by one, late into the night. With each one, another shocking piece of the puzzle falls into place, and Dr. Adrienne Hale’s web of lies slowly unravels. </Summary>
		<Pages> 286 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 630456798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Freida McFadden </Author>
		<Price> AED 79.64 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Ward D </Title>
		<Summary> Medical student Amy Brenner is spending the night on a locked psychiatric ward.

Amy has been dreading her evening working on Ward D, the hospital’s inpatient mental health unit. There are very specific reasons why she never wanted to do this required overnight rotation. Reasons nobody can ever find out.

And as the hours tick by, Amy grows increasingly convinced something terrible is happening within these tightly secured walls. When patients and staff start to vanish without a trace, it becomes clear that everyone on the unit is in grave danger.

Amy’s worst nightmare was spending the night on Ward D.

And now she might never escape. </Summary>
		<Pages> 333 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 730456798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Freida McFadden </Author>
		<Price> AED 23.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> The Coworker </Title>
		<Summary> Two women. An office filled with secrets. One terrible crime that can't be taken back

Dawn Schiff is strange. At least, everyone thinks so at Vixed, the nutritional supplement company where Dawn works as an accountant. She never says the right thing. She has no friends. And she is always at her desk at precisely 8:45 a.m.

So when Dawn doesn't show up to the office one morning, her coworker Natalie Farrell—beautiful, popular, top sales rep five years running—is surprised. Then she receives an unsettling, anonymous phone call that changes everything…

It turns out Dawn wasn't just an awkward outsider—she was being targeted by someone close. And now Natalie is irrevocably tied to Dawn as she finds herself caught in a twisted game of cat and mouse that leaves her wondering: who's the real victim? </Summary>
		<Pages> 362 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 830456798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Freida McFadden </Author>
		<Price> AED 31.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> The Rumor Game </Title>
		<Summary> Reporter Anne Lemire writes the Rumor Clinic, a newspaper column that disproves the many harmful rumors floating around town, some of them spread by Axis spies and others just gossip mixed with fear and ignorance. Tired of chasing silly rumors about Rosie Riveters' safety on the job, she wants to write about something bigger.

Special Agent Devon Mulvey, one of the few Catholics at the FBI, spends his weekdays preventing industrial sabotage and his Sundays spying on clerics with suspect loyalties—and he spends his evenings wooing the many lonely women whose husbands are off at war.

When Anne’s story about Nazi propaganda intersects with Devon’s investigation into the death of a factory worker, the two are led down a dangerous trail of espionage, organized crime, and domestic fascism—one that implicates their own tangled pasts and threatens to engulf the city in violence. </Summary>
		<Pages> 368 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 930456798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Thomas Mullen </Author>
		<Price> AED 52.10 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> The Split </Title>
		<Summary> Jane Connor is resigned to being the “plain Jane” of her family—pragmatic and dependable—so unlike her beautiful and impetuous younger sister Esme. When Esme calls Jane during a flash summer storm, announcing she’s left her high-society husband, Jane is shocked to learn her sister wishes to stay with her. Could this be an opportunity for them to become close again? The only catch: Esme needs a ride from the city to their small Connecticut hometown, and Jane is terrified of getting on the highway because of what she did when they were teens. Jane must either let Esme stand on her own two feet for once or jump to her flighty younger sister’s rescue—and her choice cleaves her life in two.

With a rollicking pace and shocking twists and turns, The Split captivatingly explores how little we know the ones we love—and how one small choice can change everything. </Summary>
		<Pages> 288 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 330056798999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Kit Frick </Author>
		<Price> 54.00 AED </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Salem's Cipher </Title>
		<Summary> A brilliant code breaker shatters a centuries-old conspiracy and unravels her own family secrets in an addictive and heart-pounding thriller by Edgar Award–nominated author Jess Lourey.

Salem Wiley is a genius cryptanalyst. She’s also a loner who prefers a safe and familiar path. Until her mother disappears in the wake of a brutal murder, leaving behind a cryptic warning of threats to come. Forced out of her safe zone, Salem embarks with her best friend, Bel, on a dangerous quest that reaches back centuries into America’s hidden history.

Drawn into a labyrinth of messages encrypted by Emily Dickinson and hidden in the legendary Beale Cipher, Salem discovers her mother’s double life—and the truth. An ancient and ruthless society is hell-bent on ruling the world, and only a select group of hunted women stands in its way. </Summary>
		<Pages> 412 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 330456008999 </ISBN>
		<Author> Jess Lourey </Author>
		<Price> AED 23.00 </Price>
	</book>
	
	<book>
		<Title> Day One </Title>
		<Summary> Marty seems to do no wrong. Trent can’t seem to get things right. When they are thrown together by tragedy, their futures may be defined by one What really happened on Day One?

Stonesmere is an English seaside suburb defined by poignant traditions passed from generation to generation, and the bonds of small town community spirit. But when a lone gunman disrupts a school assembly, he sets of a chain of events that throws this close-kint town into turmoil.

Marty is a golden girl, albeit one sometimes in the shadow of her father’s accomplishments and the care of her mother—an outsider who became a beloved teacher. Meanwhile, Trent’s home life is in the only child of a mother forever on the lookout for the boyfriend who can remake their lives, Trent longs for Stonesmere’s stability. But he and his mother only pass through. </Summary>
		<Pages> 368 </Pages>
		<ISBN> 330256798109 </ISBN>
		<Author> Abigail Dean </Author>
		<Price> AED 40.00 </Price>
	</book>
</library>
